cards laid out for show star shine is so bright watch the secrets unfold there's magic in her hands
whisper what the future holds dance to the mystery yeah yeah yeah so
let the tarot move with the rhythm
We are Kangol
Hi guys! Okay, we have 20 people in here already, so I do have some exciting news.
Okay, I've got a new video.
I've got a new video, mate. I haven't seen it yet. How are you guys doing? What's up, J-Dog?
How's it going? Well, it's exciting now because it's National World Goat Day. Okay, that's exciting,
but I did...
Get a new AI video. Mike sounds good. Okay. So you have 20 people. So I think that's
gonna be good to premiere it. So I don't know. I looked up holidays. It's August 21st, right?
And I said, what holiday? Then I said, World Goat Day. So, uh, no, I had to wait for 20 people
to be here. Someone left. So when 20 people get here, I will start. Hey, Charisma, how are you?
Hi guys!
Oh, who lost it?
You know, I did, uh...
I did...
I'm modding, but I'm going to do some remodding.
But, let me see...
How are you guys, though? I hope you guys are good.
Okay.
I got this open.
I like you too, Halo, okay.
I like you too, Frog.
Thank you for being here.
Scarlet, thank you.
Spunky, you too.
I can't forget you, sweetheart.
I don't know, somehow I always have more mods
than I did before,
You know what?
A few of you may, I might just need a little,
a little time, but, okay.
Twenty people? Okay, are you ready?
Tell me when, uh,
I need someone to say, uh, yeah, I got it, I got it.
Uh, are you ready, guys?
I'm excited.
Let me get a, let me get a cigar for this.
A little celebration.
I got my Starbucks too.
I had a little Starbucks. Okay. 23 people. Okay. I do have a new video. It is probably
or maybe a song you've heard, but I think the video will be cool. And so I did this one, but
oh, is the lecture here? The lecture is here? Oh, lecture. Hey, you're here too. Okay. I made
a new video. Okay. Almost 30 people. I'll wait till 30 people get here. I'll wait till 30. Oh,
yeah. I'll wait till 30 people. Two more people.
I have I made a new video, and I'm really excited to watch it. I haven't seen it yet, but I've seen like the
Storyboard I think it's gonna be pretty cool guys. I just have a feeling
and
See how you guys like it and we'll see how it goes. Okay. Well 28 people
Goat and tarot is devil energy temptation habits, but also raw persistence and survival also
Capricorn is the devil and also the goat, right?
And so we got that, too.
Okay, 28 people.
Well, it's like, yeah.
Go talk with the total devil energy.
Well, I hope you guys like this.
I'm glad I'm able to create some stuff.
Jenny-jen, how are you?
Is my friend Jenny-jen?
Oh, I know Jenny-jen.
Jenny-jen.
Some people, okay?
25 people. Okay. Well before I lose anybody else
And it's gonna be cool. I think it would be cool. Should I wait for 30 now? Let's just do it
Little bit I'm a little bit a little nervous. I'm just like
Now people are leaving so I'll just wait till 30 people, but yeah, we can chat for a little bit, you know
It was interesting day yesterday
Yeah, so so happy
Happy you guys are here. Hey Nancy. Okay. Well, I think we got oh
Wow, we're losing people. Okay, so always 30 people live before I will premiere the video
But it'll be cool. We can talk about our stuff
You know, it was really interesting yesterday like I was you know on beat a show
you know sometimes I have you know I try to stick to my own show usually but I
look you know I love Vita and she got she really did give me started here and
so yeah so what happened was my camera at one time kind of went like this
On the table, and maybe it was a little bit more messy than it is now, you know
See there's some probably tobacco and stuff, whatever. There's a tobacco on it. It turned into like
There it turned into like it got posted on some ip2 network by this person kissed my cheeks and
Eldo was involved. They're just haters. There's I mean it's like Eldo was the first at one point like a lot of people
Wow, we're losing people. Okay, that's kind of bad
So I guess the video premieres postponed a little bit so we lost half the half the chat, but it'll be worth it
It'll be worth it
So I'll just finish this story
Basically it turned into this whole
Thing oh
Go, you know, oh what? Oh my god. Look how messy look how messy that your floor is it wasn't even the floor is the table
I'm gonna switch it back on the table.
And then it turned into like,
it just got really,
honestly it got really ugly.
It got some really negative things were said.
It was just, it's trolling.
And it's like, I did find out it was like
these IP2 trolls,
the elder was IP2 trolls,
just my cheeks,
because they're on the server, right?
I don't know why.
And it's like, I didn't,
I'm not, I wasn't never met,
never met him.
He came back on the show like once after he was gone for a few months and with any it was like, you know saying
Something against TOS and so I kicked them off the piano
But he hates me now apparently like some other people. I guess it's just a fun
hate train sometimes, but it turned into like oh
you know
It turned into like, oh, we're calling PETA, there's cats shit everywhere, but it's just
really ugly.
The more I try to explain, carefully, it might be watching, oh, who cares, who cares.
Well, it can't get any worse than it's already gotten, I mean, it's like the worst, it's
like, and it's like, especially, you know, my cats are my, like, my life, right, I love
They have Rudy over there and Tricks and Lola, like they're all sleeping, like here you can see Rudy over there, I'll show you now.
There's Rudy at the TV, okay, and then there's Lola right there, and then there's Tricks over there, let's see if he's over here.
So they're all good. Okay, it's okay Jen.
Yeah, I understand, and it's like also there's so much stuff said, I know it like...
Some people are like, oh my god, like I think you know some people probably believe some stuff
I don't I'm not saying talk so plus Moses. Yeah, I've heard of talk so plus Moses
All right, I don't believe I have it
But hey, okay, so anyway, it just got really ugly beaded did up stick up for me, right? Yeah
Maybe you huh
But it's like
But now it's turned into something where it's like then some of the people was one of the chat they named some psyches floored
It's just they're caught constantly. Oh, I have shit all over me. I don't know. It's like it's just like very negative like kind of like
Thanks, I posted a couple cool thing. It is bullying. Yeah, I don't want the IP to audience here
I mean
Because I mean I like IP to creators like you know, St. Benny
You know, like there's the great creators, but it's turned into like
The creators are considered low-cows by the audience and they basically
Hate the audience hates. I mean, it's like it's really weird. I saw they're desperate for streamers
Well, I mean, I guess I guess I finally made IP2 because I was you know, they the person kissed my cheeks
Clipped the picture of the tobacco on the on the table. It's like, oh my god. Look at his floor
It was not my floor. It was just my table. It was tobacco on it. You can see it. You can see what happens
I already cleaned my table, but here's what happens
Look because I have these like cigar things they're like you see and so it gets kind of messy, right?
It's like
But yeah, it gets kind of like there's tobacco, right? It's like yeah, so I mean it's like
It was really easy just to
You know wipe up and stuff, but
I don't know it's turned into like I'm some kind of disgusting monster
Basically, oh, we're calling PETA on you or we're calling you know animal control
you're
abusing your animal love
Like a really negative shit
hurtful it's like it'd be just kind of like
You know even though people say oh pet, you know your cats aren't like you're you know, they're of course
They're not human being children, but it's like they are
Like my kids it's closest all over get the kids right it's having my my cats and I love my cats and it's hurtful, okay?
but anyway, I
Don't know I just want I just want to let you know guys know because you'll probably see if I go anywhere. It'll probably say oh
Those they'll say a lot of shit like a lot of shit's been said like
Yeah, I did I saw I was there actually watching and I saw
Yeah
It's like it was and it wasn't even my floor wasn't even shown they're like show your floor
Maybe my floor is fine. I didn't kind of I did vacuum a little bit
But yeah, I have actually was supposed to get a hardwood floor because that's easier to clean
but
You know having cats and I've had three liters of kittens and stuff like that and it's like, you know, I would love to
Unfortunately, and I was actually at one point supposed to, but you know, things happen and things happen and
Unfortunately that got swept under the you know that that got
The kibosh kibosh or something. Yeah
But I'm not and I'm certainly not perfect and it's like, you know
And that's what I was I was like and these people that are say this elbow and the kiss my cheeks
I mean, they did go on the panel talking, but they're not on
video they're not
I know Elda may have been a stream maybe streams like I saw a key stream one time or something like that
But uh, you know, I'm certainly not perfect and it's like I'm not gonna judge people and like the man
Oh, show me your floor. Show me every nook and cranny of your apartment
They were look for every like little speck of dirt and say like you're some kind of disgusting monster
I mean that's just what it kind of turned into and it's like oh wow. I didn't cry about it. I was trying to get
You know explain a little bit bit
You know, I don't need to explain the people that matter, don't care, the people that do
matter, don't care, the people that don't matter, just blow it out of proportion, right?
It's just trolling.
The girl kissed my cheeks was even like, she's like, oh, I don't care about your cat, I care
about what your plural looks like.
So I don't know, it was stupid, but just so you guys know, yeah, I'm just going to brush
But I do want you guys to know because it's like, I don't want you to be surprised when you see people
harassing me and like stuff like that and I hope that and also I've had donators
harass a little bit. I will say like, you know, maybe if you
Would like to avoid that and still support me. You know, you can't you know, you can do anonymously through cash up or other ways
You know, but I should get a cheap like dollar store quality litter box
Yeah, I will but the thing is I like I had a litter box for Rudy when Rudy came because Rudy was very
He was like under the bed under the bed for a while
so I had a litter box there and stuff the other cats really didn't use it and
I have a cat door so they can go in and out as they please and most of them
Outside like, you know, probably 60 70% of the time also, you know, they bring up really hurtful things like oh
You let your cat got eaten by a coyote. You let your cat get hit by a car. Unfortunately indoor outdoor cats there are
Hazards and sometimes that happens, but also I think for my cats
Not a male cat soup and also there's like, oh, you don't have any you don't you know tricks is not neutered. Okay, but
Lola is Rudy is
and
You know Lenora's and
Tricks with trick but tricks is not really a wanderer and it's like and then in this person. What's their name?
She was like oh lady Bathory who's always been a troll of me. She's like well. I offer to you know pay for you know
neutering the cat never I
If someone offers like one of my cats like free like a free medical care, of course, I would take you
You know, I would take them up on the offer, but they never did
Okay
Yeah, yeah, there's some cool litter box and stuff. I mean, it's just like but I don't I don't know
There's different opinions about it, but I do have a nice backyard. I do have
So the cats never had a the cats are smart people are thinking like the cats cats don't just shit all over the floor
And so anyway
If I had a litter box, they'd say oh, it's not clean
You know it is a box of shit in a room, right?
If you have a litter box, so it's like it's not like
You know that like, you know look that great anyway, but anyway
You guys understand, okay, so we have 31 people here
So I'm gonna premiere the video and hopefully you guys like this. This is the new new video
Let's see. I haven't seen it yet either. I hope you guys
If you guys enjoy before anybody else, please I'm just gonna be sorry 29 people. That's fine. Okay. Please enjoy guys
Okay
of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight crowds came running just to see the flame
but envy was the price of fame and now he stands where the echoes fall with terror
Yeah, I like that. I love it. Beautiful. I think it was pretty beautiful.
Let me see if anyone can come up. Like I said, guys, I'm just doing the kibosh on the, you know, having...
Sponsored panels or whatever, but I do I will offer, you know banner advertising if you guys would like to have like, you know
Any kind of advertising on a banner for like $10 an hour
You know, whatever you want on the banner and I will also
Verbally like read your read your ad and you can put it in the chat, too
And so I think that's reasonable and then I
Don't know so I hope that is like better
Also, if you go to my website, I don't know if it's there, let me see if my link tree
is set up with it.
Is Arthur?
Hold on.
Yeah.
Make sure it's Arthur.
Yo.
Good morning, beloved sir.
Hello.
How are you?
I'm doing great.
I'm just following two things.
Maybe psyche could, you know, maybe hit another good intro after we reach maybe like 50 likes or something, you know
To and maybe I hope this isn't bother you, but I
Don't know. Could you tell me what AI application you used?
Yeah, well, I use a few because I use, you know, I do use chat CPT and I'll tell you guys I'll tell you guys to you know
To make the video specifically the animator videos, okay the animation it is a website called neural
Brains neural frames
narrow
any
Neurl frames, and it is like I do have like a premium subscription. I think it's a little bit pricey
You know, it's pricey. It's pricey to make the videos, but you know, it is really great quality. There's several
options for I guess the the rendering software you can use and some are more expensive than others and
You know, but I think I've used the same
rendering software for each of the videos and stuff like that, but also the music is like I
come up with the concept of it and
discuss it with ChatGPT and then get the lyrics through ChatGPT and then there's another website that I
put the lyrics through to create the music and stuff like that and I choose
you know what kind of music
style goes with it and
That kind of thing and it gives you two off and so yeah, and I'm free me
I'm on up on all these things and so it doesn't get a little bit a little bit pricey
But you know, I'm sure that these prices will go down in time and things like that as the technology
Continues to improve. That's gonna be more and more amazing. I think it's gonna like think more and more a really
I play on doing more more of these and you know
I just I think I should tell you though like the first time I used the that neural frames
I thought it was like, you know unlimited video creation
But it is a credit system and I did go above some of the credits and so just make sure that
You know it will create a storyboard for you and just just know that it's like
you know
I'm on I'm on the I think the neural frames. I think I'm on the $40 plan
Yeah, that's my month. I
Mean definitely that's my competition is good because with competition it creates
More business meaning other people are gonna want, you know, maybe to lower their prices knowing that there's more competition. So
Yeah, and I also, if you guys are interested, like, I can't, you know, along with, like, offering private terror readings, which you can, like, I think you can book through the, like, the psychicawakens.com right now.
But you can also, you know, if you'd like to do other stuff, like, you know, besides just the terror reading, I will do, you know, consulting on burning a YouTube channel, and I can tell you, like, a lot of...
Lot of I can tell you a lot of stuff. I basically have a look, you know, I have a lot of knowledge I've gained and
Also, I can tell you how I do the prompts and how I talk to AI which is like kind of the key
I found and of how it like how I talked to it and
Basically, I can give you a lot of good tips tips with it and stuff like that
And so I think and I think it's pretty reasonable for consulting. I'm not charging that was the doll. I'm just charging
You know, I'm charging very reasonable
Last question. Last question. Damn, I forgot what I was going to ask, fuck.
It's okay. It's okay.
Damn it. I guess I'll go out with saying this. You've gotten so advanced. I remember when
you were initially doing the whole chat, PBTAI, and now look at you, man. You're doing the
That application. Oh, two questions. Do you use a laptop or are you using your phone for all this?
Well, the first videos I made I just had my tablet and but then I just you know
I was able to buy a computer this month
Thanks to you know kind donations. I was able to and so this you know
This is through the computer, but you can just use you can do it through a tablet
It's just it doesn't really know that the power is you know on their servers
I think with some of it so it's like you can use a tablet or any
Cell phone you can use from right. Yeah, okay. That's that's one and then the last question
Can you put anybody's face on it and then create AI?
Yes, you can't mean it's like there's different ways of doing it like, you know, especially with images
Yes, you can put anybody's face on it and you can also like I could I could have put an image in but the way
But the way I did it it basically goes by the the words and the song and stuff like that. Yeah
The storyboard I think it can be tweaked and things like that and you can also put sample images in but I like I kind of like
Yeah, it goes by the lyrics. Okay, and you know, I guess there's certain applications
that you know it requires you to only use yourself you know it won't allow others
I don't think these are real people like you know it's like I don't think it's using anybody else's
image and but if you wanted to you could yes and I also like you know and also I pretty much have gone
You know if I was to ever share stuff I would get the person's permission, you know
But it's like you know most people would be kind of I don't think it's illegal to use a likeness a likeness of somebody because it's not like
Using very sack everything, but yeah, I think I've come up with some pretty good good
Results with this and you know with my tarot deck too. I'm creating a tarot deck and I've done it
You can see them on my community wall. You can see I did Alexander mayor a card. I did I've done page
Oh, no, I've done beta a card. I've done
I've done a lot of people look hard and most people have enjoyed the results.
The person that says in the chat that, you know, please give the cats to a good home
and stuff like that.
You know, go fuck yourself, really.
It's like just really go fuck yourself.
That is like just cruel and you're just a troll and I know it's like you're trying to
hurt my feelings or whatever, but you know, it's really like, you know, I'm not, I have
my windows open.
I'm not blowing smoke at the cats, I mean, you know, I do, it's like, you know, I don't
It's just like if you're in people are just gonna pick at all these little things about about me and stuff like that forever
About it, but you know what I take great care of my cats and it's like
Cats are fine. They're not eating tobacco. I know it's like a cat eat tobacco
Yes, but my cats are don't eat tobacco the cats are smart enough to know the difference in catnip and tobacco
And this cat that actually gets them high and so the cats have never I've never seen my cat interested in tobacco or anything
And so yeah, you'll be hidden and anybody else that's gonna say horrible things about me
It's like I'm not gonna put up with it. Yeah, just get out of here. It's not funny to me
It's not funny to me. I know it's funny just like some other channels like they might think oh, you know, it's a joke or whatever
It's like
Seriously, it's uh, you know, they're my they're my babies. Okay. And so yeah
Oh well, please oh Empress Chinchilla whatever okay
Empress Chinchilla so this so this is a porn pop porn bomber from ip2 that doesn't ever go on camera, right?
I just have shit all over my walls right guys like, you know, it's all over my walls all
People are saying it's all over the floors all over the walls guys. I'm here every day, you know, I I don't know
I mean, it's like we're gonna say these things some people are gonna believe it
But it's like people who are gonna believe something like that and just judge me like that. They're not they're not real
They're not real
They're not they're just trolls. They're just trolling. Okay, and there's kiss my cheeks
Okay, so kiss my cheeks is gonna come up and kiss my cheeks. I don't you can just talk in chat and make your point in chat because
Yesterday in betas kiss my cheeks was the one that went on the IP to server
Posting the photos and everything saying that oh look at his floor
Saying that I'm a drug addict don't donate to this person. I'm
Beg for money for fish sauce. I don't know so anyway, you can just talk in chat and make your point in chat
Okay, ever since she'll is a male. Okay. Well anyway
Kiss my cheeks. I think we talked enough last night and I really don't feel like you were fair to me and so
I'm not, you know, I'm not trying to silence your voice, but just talk in chat if you have a point to make, okay?
Maybe I'll have you on later if we can like come to like a reasonable
Dialogue, but I don't I think you're not on camera or anything
So I don't know if you're gonna be some kind of form bomber or and we're bomber and so go ahead and
Like so not and like and we're bomber is that somebody that says the n-word several times trying to get neutral. So anyway
How about that? Okay
And you or you can just type in a private chat, but if you want to have a dialogue you can talk in the chat
Okay, I'm not gonna ban you unless you're sort of saying disrespectful shit in the chat, but I really am a
You know, I just don't like how how you talk to me and the attitude of it and it is
This this IP to server it was called I left it. I was in it for summers at the might have been elder server
It's called quips and clips
And the day before yesterday,
they had someone posted a link that it literally was H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T dot G-A-Y.
Okay, so that is the kind of attitude these people have in it.
This is what they think is normal,
is like promoting a G-A-Y-H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T.
Nothing I want to be involved in, okay?
Um, it's just kind of scary. I did share with you to the other day
I was like look what they're posting in this like this is coming up on my screen
You know, it's like besides people saying I have HIV and all these other things and also, um, you know
who was
Who was laughing about that yesterday was Hannah and it's like I know Hannah's got salty because it's gaudy time to her out
but
She's gonna laugh about that or make jokes about HIV and it's like and I was always on you know always on her side
And the plus I was like, you know what she came attacking gaudy and stuff and these people and they didn't do anything
They were they were being very cordial and they have been lately. And so
Yeah, so Hannah, you know, it's like that was gonna like, you know, I
Left from discord
Oh trip and sip so that's trip and sip. Okay. Yeah, I left the discord because yeah because
You're posting things attacking me saying look at look at this, you know excrement everywhere and it's not yeah
I mean, it's really is it is like this. I've never seen bullying this
severe
Even for the IPG people, but maybe there has been and I'm sure that yeah, I've seen some locales get
Attacked but you know, I think I'm getting it kind of kind of kind of bad and
It's like people I thought were friends are just like
Thinking I'm like some disgusting joke and you know people just said really bad thing. I have a I'm a sensitive person, you know
Why aren't you out walking like be that?
Because I'm streaming right now. She was streaming through the night and now she's walking. I
You know slept woke up
And now I'm streaming.
Maybe I'll take a walk in a little bit,
but we have different schedules.
And so you don't have to like,
and indeed I'm not the same person where we have different.
Yeah.
It's not like they were lying.
Yes, they were because first of all,
that was on my floor, that was not excrement.
It was tobacco on my table.
Looks like I need to show you right now.
This is the exact same thing.
It's not even any different than this.
Guys, you see, there's tobacco on the table, right?
That's what it is.
Because I have these cigars that I put in a, right?
So that's it.
Extraman right it's tobacco, which is they're both brown, but I can show you it's just tobacco, okay?
And I could it's easily wiped up
I mean it's like so I'm not gonna argue about it trip and sip or whatever your name is you know
I know your IP to troll and all you're here to do is try to upset me call me a little cow or whatever and
Her damn is my reputation and you know make a joke out of me
And I'm not gonna let you do it and everybody look there's that person right there
And there's a few of them in the chat,
not like I'm gonna block them right now or anything,
unless people say something really bad or break the TOS.
But, when have you ever trolled me?
Well, I don't know, but what is the H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T dot G-A-Y?
Not, well, maybe you are,
and that's why you're still in the chat, okay?
But what is that, why are you,
why are people posting about G-A-Y-H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T
in your server?
I would have deleted that post right away, right?
It's just seems disgusting to me, okay?
Plus it was just trolling, oh my God, look at this person.
I just saw you, and I was like, why am I in the server?
And I was like, yeah, it's good to maybe be able
to monitor some of the stuff.
But I was like, I remember when I was in this one server,
it was like, I think it was Kate's or something,
and Allied AMC kept, while I was on the show,
kept posting, and I would see his posts,
and it was like,
Well, he's just trying to distract it. It's just a distraction. So I'm not um, yeah
So anyway guys, you know
That's all I have to say about that really, you know, I'm uh
It is it is unfair it is
overblown it is and it's like the more the more I try to defend myself then it's
like oh you look it's guilty and if you don't defend yourself oh you're good so
it's like it's not a not any benefit to me to continue the dialogue about it so
let's just I'm just gonna okay so now trip and sip now you went too far okay
and so trip and sip is banned okay bye
I mean, it's really simple. I mean, I don't have to go, you know, go talk that shit somewhere else. Yeah, I'm sorry Amanda
I hope you're okay, man. Let me see what I mean
Okay, and the cats my cats have never eaten tobacco. They don't even eat well
They do eat cat in it, but they know the difference. They don't eat in during tobacco
I mean, it's just like you're just being stupid. Okay?
You're being stupid. They also can't you know cats can't eat certain vegetables. They can't eat avocado, but I can still have you know
uh guacamole and stuff and they're not gonna go eat the guacamole right it's like
i don't know my cats are not well i'm not like i'm i would feed it you know i'm not feeding anything
and basically i'm here i just don't eat the back of it's not it's not appetizing for cats
My phone, man, you know, I had a phone call, you know, me always getting phone calls.
A busy, busy man.
Awesome.
I just wanted to say it real quick, because I didn't get to leave without saying my good
bye, sir.
You have a good day.
And everyone got to hit up the thumbs up, man.
It ain't hard.
It's free.
It ain't cost anything.
Uh, uh, it's like I'm being nosy right now.
Are you...?
Are you using your phone's camera or your tablet's camera or your webcam for for modding?
Oh, right now I have I have a I have like a
Camera that it was like eight dollars. I'm actually my
Tricks started biting the cord and everything and it's a cheap camera
So I I'm returning it and I'm getting a new camera today, but I'm using this little cheap webcam for now
Okay, and yeah, and I use my tablet for modding right now, which I can do
and also this person talking about um bestiality and stuff you know what yeah this person knows
in chat i've already blocked but it's like you know this is like it's just getting really
really slanderous and like you know um please uh if you mod see stuff like that like please just
hide it i just i saw that comment they made and it's yeah it's really uh it's really
really offensive. It's putting disturbing images and I know you're just trying to get me associated
with these disturbing images, but it's really, really out of bounds and it's just showing your
character, not mine. It's like if you go to my community wall, you'll see a post that's talking
about, you know, let them judge you, let them, you know, say whatever they want to, but you just...
I'm just gonna keep being me and it's like and I'm just gonna keep shining my light. I'm not gonna be
I'm not gonna be
You know being dragged down by this. Okay. This is just gonna bring me higher. This is just I'm just gonna like
I'm alchemizing all this negativity. It's just yeah, so
Not hurting me. Yeah. Is there any way that you can get like a tripod so you could put the webcam on top that way, you know
It's like angled down. Yeah, I mean I I do I do have it. I mean I yeah
I want to get a better try but it is up on something. I try I'll have to angle a little better
Yeah, that's a lot better. That's a lot better. I was uh, yeah, so you know, I'm working on it
A lot of stuff going on so it's good brother. Thank you. Thank you, Arthur. Hey, man. You do thing man. Take care
Yeah, um, yeah, Nancy it's just getting crazy and then it's like
You know, that's why I'm probably I'm gonna have to avoid going on
Yeah, I am the scapegoat on goat day, right?
And also capricorn capricorns are used to being scapegoats too
because
As the devil, you know how the devil's a scapegoat and everyone blames the devil
Oh, the devil made me do it this kind of stuff even it's actually our own our own nature or we are
this higher and lower nature and
We have a shadow guys
There's also a really good video. I posted a music video called projections and it's a really good song. It's by this
group called night
Night something so it's really good. That's really good if you want to listen to it Tommy James made Tommy James
Me Tommy James made you do it or what? What are you saying a little writer?
Tommy made you do it. What do you mean?
The internet's acting up. Okay
Can I hug the cats? Yes, I can. You can see right here, Rudy is over here
looking himself over there, right? And then there's Lola
He's having a little nappy, and then there's Trinx up here
sleeping on blankets and pillows. I show, you know, I I shared with Bita
some pictures of my cat door or my kitchen and
You know, there's really nice little outdoor cat thing I have.
Let me see.
In the IPQ discord, Empress Chinchilla has evidence of se-
Okay, so this is disgusting, and can-
Okay, this is also the porn bomber that he pornbombed at and tried to pornbomb me, okay?
This McDonald's person right there, and so just consider the source when you hear this
shit.
It's like this- it just bothers me that some people will believe this bullshit, but-
Oh my gosh, I'm sorry, everybody don't shit too much, hold on.
I just need to, yeah, oh, they retracted the message.
Well, I won't save you, my friend, not my friend, but that will not prevent you from
being hit in from my chat, because you are a form bomber, and just be aware, guys,
that you form bomb BDS today, try to form bomb me, and now it's saying that, you know,
these allegations again. So, you know what?
They're just they're just revealing themselves. Okay, I'm gonna pull my feel like I'm on tiktok right now
Cuz sometimes they get a little sexy on tiktok, you know, and in the shorts or whatever
But yeah, I'm trying to see that's why I'm a little bit careful with angling it too low. Yeah
Get a life. I mean get a life. We're really I mean, what is so
But it's gone wrong in their life where they have to do this to people really
Okay
Really, what is what I mean? It's like sad. I feel I'm almost like what happened to them that they're
Have to be so cruel to somebody and I was like it is cruelty. It's bullying and cruelty
Yeah, so the mods can't he's blocking all the mods like
He's not I don't know how they do in there and you always see they're hidden now. They're hidden now, so
But they didn't just retract the statement so that they
Mods can see it. I guess it is sad
But you know what? Just let them reveal themselves, right?
I'll give them a mask. I'll give them the they have the ability just to hide behind their
You know a little avatar troll account, whatever. They're not it's just like they're so irrelevant why?
But it's like and some things are so active and they all agree they all seem to
Just like it's like an echo chamber with some of the stuff and of course with
Discussing allegations or, you know, HIT, LER does, and I don't, you know, not quoting
me because I respect this person, but this person didn't understand about manipulation
and stuff like that.
The quote is, a lie repeated often enough becomes the truth because people just, that
becomes the truth.
And so, right, you can press block and then you can't see what he typed.
Oh yeah.
So he's blocking the mods and so the mods can't get him.
I get it.
I got you.
Um, and, okay, so this is, uh, uh, see that person, uh, Tucker Dick, yeah, I mean, people
that are gonna repeat this, I mean, if maybe you just, you weren't aware, but, you know,
if you didn't hear my whole explanation, or, you know, you know, bye.
Whew, guys.
Yeah, so, yeah, they have little tricks that they use.
Hopefully, this will all go in the book.
my trolls because I've had some you know epic trolling not not in a good way it's
just like the worst but I know how to deal with it okay and so most of these
comments people can't even see oh also you might have top chat on because
yeah a little right I don't know if you're gonna be funny or whatever yeah I
mean that's again the serial that it was tricks
For the matrix or also tricks because I had magic and then magic and tricks so
I can't do that, Ebel McDonald.
If you say that again, because I've already explained that to you several times, that
I'm not doing this.
Thank you, Elector.
I'm not, yeah.
I've already explained I'm not the one that has any control over the handles coming up
as the name.
It's something that YouTube does on some channels.
I have no idea.
Right.
There's like little roaches, guys, just like play whack-a-mole, they're going to pop up
different accounts.
That that kiss my cheeks. I said go ahead and say what you want to in chat. They did it, right?
Yeah, this person that's using that photo. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. I
Don't care what and that's like and so when people say that stuff. Yeah, of course they did. Yeah, of course they did
Or and you know, that's them. It's kind of unfortunate that
You know, sometimes free memberships are awarded to people that are just actively assholes a little bit of chaos
Yeah, I don't know. They have nothing yet. They have nothing better to do
They sit wait wait like they're waiting for me and other people to come on and just harass them and
They have no life
They're not doing any streaming of their own for the most part. I don't think you know or
If they are, hey, and I don't know if this is the real SIPA. Is this the real SIPA or is this the fake SIPA?
Because there's a fake
Or SIPA and Jamie knows Jamie knows SIPA
There's a really good SIPA. I don't want them to be confused, but there's a troll SIPA
That just uses the same. So we'll see who it is. Jamie and Jamie knows the real one
so she will be able to
To
What's it called to verify it is you okay, Jamie? Let me know. Okay. I can actually check to see if
So it looks like yes, you are the real sip. Oh, hey, what's up? Hold on
Hey, good to see you. I haven't seen you for a long time and it's awesome to see you. Yeah, check check you and
Yeah, and yeah, I
Really glad that you're here and also I hope that
You come you come more often because I do miss you and stuff and it's like and I know that I
Know I know that some stuff was said and like, you know
I'm trying I really am trying to ban those words like from my chat
They've been on the F H E G O T and stuff like that and stuff like, you know, I called it and stuff too
It's just like I mean, I don't want you to be offended. Okay, so
I'll try to do a better job of protecting people.
It's a very satisfying virtual to act the way they do online.
There's no consequence, at least no consequence, that they can amuse you to see.
Yeah, but it's just like, it's just basically they're just a nasty kind of energy.
They're trying to spread and hatred, you know, chaos and stuff, but I know how to deal with
chaos.
Yeah, it's still real simple.
Okay.
Yeah, I looked at the account. I'm able to in the mods also you can click on the name and then go to the channel
I saw that it was the real the real one, but there has been a fake one
I don't know if you know that's a sepah there has been a fake
sepah going around trolling to recently and so that's why I was
Asking if it was the real one, but I'm really glad to hear
Yeah, and I think lowrider yeah, you see my intelligent and
Maybe I'm I hope I'm not like just
Being too free with the things that I really do want people to be able to post and if they're
Yeah, I
Know a lecture, but also I
Want to bring attention to them. I just like they're trying like they're satisfied with that. Well, you know
Not being looked at in a good way, and so that's called it see
Yeah, hey and Vicky
Yeah, oh Vicky yeah
Well Vicky Gotti
Rain JT and Ziggy and I I'm trying to make peace
I think I have unless it's a huge bluff and everything, but I don't think I don't think so. I think that
Basically, I think I've come to an agreement with people
It gives them a okay. Well, maybe it does but then I hope it when they are blocked it quickly goes away and then
Gets even worse when they realize that it's like they're just exposed
I do want to call out the name because I want people to know the names because a lot of these are form bombers
Okay, the dopamine hit a lot by a lot of these are form bombers and I don't want people to be aware of the names
Okay, so I want them to become known as
Trolls and so people don't think they're serious because a lot of them are using other people's names that are legitimate, right?
So and I don't want to people to confuse people and so I just want to make sure I
Call out some of the names that I see when I'm being porn bombs
Because I have been formed on over a hundred times
So now I have seen all the real names and things like that, but I do understand I'm not trying to give them
Fuel that's a narcissist lives for the fuel or psychopath
There's also a question you can ask people and there's it's a certain question that psychopaths can't answer
Because they don't understand it. It says do you know that by saving a
Person's life that you're saving worlds, right?
it's
Nancy no, I mean they don't they don't
They don't because they get attention elsewhere. Maybe so
They're celebrated elsewhere. There's some chats where they seem to be celebrated and it's just fun
people are
They're these like folk heroes and something so I'm just trying to like let you know
Who these people are so yeah, maybe I will start to not acknowledge them
But I kind of point out some stuff and yeah, and so yeah, do you see these people?
You can just, again, I know the energy, I'm not gonna say the name, like, it takes, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, I hope, I think, I think I might, I think I might have though, I think I might have, okay?
I think I might have made peace.
And that looks like, that looks like the, yeah, I know that for, okay.
So, I, there are a lot of relationships with people like that.
You know, then there are a lot of also trolls here like like trolls that I like and I'm friends with and so it's like
But the problem is when they if they start to troll me, right? Or I was well, everybody
There's some trolling that's fine. I mean I can troll too, right, but
It's like I just know I just know the difference. I'm learning the difference now. Oh, yeah
That was confirmation on honk at the moment, so
anyway as I
Hide these people. I just but I need you guys to be aware that they're gonna be blocking mods
So multiple people to see there. They're what they're saying sometimes and
So I don't know
I'm just gonna I'm just gonna go with my gut on stuff and how you know, I do appreciate
And I know you guys are looking out for me and it's kind of by this and stuff. So
Anyway
I don't think, yeah, I don't think, and I do like Gotti,
like Gotti, you know, and I have had a lot of talks recently,
like, and, you know, we're on a show,
he's been on the panel a lot, but we were on a show
on our friend Alex Mayer's show,
and he was on for several hours and had a great,
Really really good conversation and respectful and come come to some understandings
And I like to do astrology too, and I can see in people's but I read about their birthday and stuff like that or the chart
I can see
Maybe why some people have the personality they do and I love understood coming to understandings
But it's like some people you can't come to an understanding with and so
If it's not going to be anything where I can have an open dialogue, then I don't mind.
Okay, and so yeah, Maria, yeah, I think maybe you, I really hope I have because, you know,
I know I did read maybe our, our conversation or, you know, some emoji conversation we had
and stuff like that because, but I was just trying to kind of clear my name because I
think some things were said that were maybe not 100% accurate, you know, but, okay.
Yeah, you know CFF and
Like I said, I figured out I'm a mod for the CFF. I mean I don't know how it's like some of these things happen
Also, like a lot of people
Yeah, and in the chat, you know, I think that I don't think they're bad people
but it's like I think it's better to make peace and
Find acceptance rather than
But I'm but that's still I'm not gonna be participating in any
negative activities no matter who I'm affiliated with okay so I'm telling you
something is the interest okay and so yeah well that's why you're not a mod
and that's why you're hidden okay bye bye I know what I'm doing okay I have I've
been raising my cats for 15 year you know I've had cats for several several
years I understand
obviously I don't need to be lectured about it. The cats are fine. I've never had a cat
ever get sick or anything from any of this or eat tobacco or out of the ash tray or anything
or off the table, okay? And so, yes, I will be more, I'll be more on top of cleaning stuff up, but yeah.
Yeah, and yeah, and I didn't say she did be there. No, be there was very uh, very defense. Oh, you're not you're not panel burst
You are just you're just trolling. So that's why you're now hidden and bye
Anyway
And I hope that is that you if that's you panel burst that's that's clipping me
Okay, I that's that you stop stop
Stop flipping my show and or that's you that's doing it that person in the chat
Stop stop, please or I will complain to rumble about it because I don't want you to do that anymore because
Now we're on bad terms, okay now you now you're pissing me off, okay?
But I didn't have any problem with it before and never did anything bad
I'm bad to you. And so what I'm talking about this person panel versus DOD, okay?
So you can just take me off of your your syndication
It's okay. They can make it a I have new cares. I mean, that's flattery. I mean, I like the
movie Abdul or something. I like that those because those AI cartoons or
whatever were clever and it was my voice and I thought they were funny and so did
other people but yeah they're gonna make some let me see the AI okay yeah okay
and calling okay wow so that kind of stuff I see that's gonna be
Nothing. That's not like the other ones were taking what I said my little calm in your routines and put it into a funny thing
and
I'm calling for like that. Whatever you just said
And I'm gonna be watching you. Okay, okay, and I never said to be dimension my cats
And so I don't know I don't trust you anymore. Okay, if you're saying shit, okay, so I
Just have to whack a mole like a mole, okay
Anyway, thanks, but no thanks. No, you're putting words in my mouth and stuff like that. Okay
Look
No, it's okay. No, I will I'm not gonna talk to them in private
I don't have access to them in private and so I just have access to them on my show right now
And so I will say that right now. Okay. Thank you
Because I left the server, and so I don't think I would be able to contact them anymore,
so that was the only way to say it, but yeah, okay, it just seems like it's a VOD, so that's
kind of the same name, but I said if it's the same person or whatever.
You know I'm trying that's what I'm saying to people come on to similar names
And so I just want to make sure I get the right person some of these people. I'm on good terms with okay
But I don't know if it's like their handle and the channel name to you
I don't know if it's for some reason they're showing the handles and not the channel names on my chat lately. Hi, Lola
You want to sit up here? See this is yes, this is this is how I can't sit. Oh, okay. Oh, but I already got it now
Okay, third female well
Okay
This is tricks his mom by the way. Well, it's tricks his mom
Yeah, and yeah
Okay, and yep your band
Okay, oh too late. No, and also that person is not
Clumsy, I think I did make peace with clumsy. They just use clumsy's photo and
and also troll him and people confuse it, but
You know now who's lame, you know, you have no voice in the chat anymore guys. I will respond to trolls because
I'm not
Reacting I'm not like I'm not
Reacting to them in a way of like
Believing them or taking what they say to heart. I'm just calling them out
Thank you. Yeah, Lola's beautiful catches sweetheart. Hey, Lola car
My sweetheart, oh, hi. Oh, I love you. I love you, too
Cats are very protective of me. They're very
Yeah, and I have to say calm energy because I don't want to upset that with like, you know erratic energy or
So I'm very calm. I'm very calm. I am very I feel like I'm calm
well
Princess Leia
No, it's just whatever
They're not bothering me like I'm cool. I'm fine with most of them
You know, I think we've come to understand it unless they start kind of like
Going after me then I have no problem. I have no problem being associated with them
I don't think they're bad people, but I just think that they were mad at me one point maybe troll
But I think we have an understanding. Okay, so
Man I stick with that. This is Rudy. Oh Rudy's up here. Hey, Rudy
Uh-oh. Hey, Lola's like, what's he doing here? You like Rudy? He's a nice he's a nice guy
See guys, it's like if cats don't like a person, they're not gonna
I'll show you. Hold on
They're not gonna do this
They're not gonna be here, they're not gonna be, Lola wouldn't be right there, right? Hi, Lola. Hi, sweetheart
She's not
Digging through ashtrays or anything she's cats are very smart. I don't know people think you know cats are and I love dogs too
But you know dogs or maybe you have to watch a little bit more because
they're not as
Independent has cats and
I don't know and there's people with dogs that are our dogs are constantly going on the floor and stuff like that
They'll just complain it. I mean it's like
Yeah, the kiddies are coming to come for me. They're my little, they're socializing.
They're sweet.
You know, I'm a very lucky guy at BreedCats, and so it's just people saying, oh, you know, we're gonna
You know, call animal control, all kinds of stuff. It's like, please, it's gonna life.
I think if dogs are cats, it equals, but cats are more independent.
Um, yeah, the cats don't give a shit cats and cats could go outside and wander the neighborhood dogs cannot
You know dogs have to be like kind of like top dogs are like the eternal three-year-olds cats are like the eternal like
No old man like Rudy's like a little little old man. He's been around he's 16 years old. Okay
So
So yeah live stream yeah, I think
I don't know exactly, yeah, you can have that conversation, but, you know, some people,
I'd like to be able to convert trolls, I don't know if some of them are just pretending
to be converted to friends, but people will always show their true colors if they have
that intention.
And so I will see, I'll have people watch it out for me and stuff like that, right?
You're lay-up in the movie Star Wars, well, people call me lay-up too because I have these
He's okay. I hope what's being posed. Okay. Yeah, well bully Hayden. You're you know, yeah, yeah, Jamie. Oh, no
I mean, it's like see this this kind of thing even if they say oh, I hope that's not yeah
And they're then repeating the allegation and stuff like that. I've already explained several times, right? And so right
Don't think I don't think so. I don't think so, but if it is I'll figure it out. I know his energy
I am a I am like, you know an intuitive and Pat that reads energy so I can recognize energy
But I don't feel it is
So
But you know, I'll you know always just theirs could be like pulling the wool over or whatever like, you know wolves
So she's clothing, but you know even
He had as an avatar. I don't think they're bad people
But if they are you start to troll me or harass anybody, you know, they won't last very long
Dogs are more loyal, but cats the cats to be very loyal as long as you you like earn their respect
dogs
People now unfortunately people that are mean to their dog the dogs still loves them and stuff like that sometimes right you've seen
Okay
Okay, yeah, well, I'm not gonna be paranoid because people can go under any name. They want to it's very easy to hide behind a name
And so I look for the energy not the name, right?
Okay
But I'll see I'll see how uh
Why a Skype
Skype a person in the chat are talking about Skype your bird guy. I had a bird to I used to have a bird a con year a cherry
Hit a con year name Lucy
And Lucy was a very sweeper when I would go be inside she would fly over to me and just like
Kind of a roll around on my that okay, so that is
Oh, is that the real Tom Flash?
Let's see if this is the real Tom Flash.
If this is not, it is the CP bomber
and I will be hiding them, but I'll see if this is a real person.
See guys, it's hard to see sometimes.
So that is the fake Tom Flash.
God, you told me it's the fake Tom Flash.
And you, instead of getting a wrench,
you will be banished into purgatory.
Not too hard to do, not too hard to figure out either.
Okay, dots can be more loyal, but it's like if you earn a cat's respect and they will be loyal to you, okay?
So yeah, that that is that he actually puts CP in the form bomb that person that discussed the disgusting
Disgusting individual and really disgusting. Okay, I know they wouldn't yeah
There's nothing but it's just like the idea of like being people trying to
Oh my god, I'm not gonna give anybody ideas. I'm just saying, you know, you don't know how low people will go
I know people have put people's pets on a
Craigslist and things like that and said oh, there's a or I don't know
There's been threats. That's why some people are very into like just keeping the pets indoors, right?
The bird cubs do a lot. We had also a green Amazon parrot named Coco, and we had an African
gray parrot. My mom did raise love birds and conures. My grandma had a canary named Dickey,
little canary name. Actually, she had like several canaries and she would name them,
always name them Dickey. And you know, they would eventually, they would sing beautifully at one
Did she get another one named a Dickey, right?
Yeah, I'm not concerned about it.
It's like I also am on good terms with the police department
and the animal control of my city.
They know me, they're aware of doxing and all of this stuff.
And so they would reach out to me first, probably by phone.
You know, they're not just gonna,
they know that I'm being harassed, right?
to see it, I don't want this to be the conversation.
Hey, Vita, how are you, Vita?
You and I have a lot of, or you and I have a lot of issues,
but I definitely think you take very good care of my cats.
I do, and I hope we don't have to, Vita,
I hope we do have, I hope we don't have issues,
like, I really don't have an issue with you at all,
like, I love you, like, all of the issue I have is like,
you get, I feel you get mad at me,
or like, sometimes you're like, well, you don't do this,
and so I don't do this, or this person's doing this,
You know, I wish I wish I wish I had done a better job at the beginning of defending you because I guess that was more important
But or important to you, but I I do apologize. Yeah, I love you and you know, I do feel like that I
Wouldn't and I'm not saying you did anything wrong, but I'm saying I
Would not let you get yelled at like I got yelled at like just and kind of like
Stuff repeated and then it's like there's a guy in your chat saying called psyche's floor
Constantly saying hi. I have shit on me and then it's like everyone's laughing in the chat
Like that's like for an hour about this. It's like, oh, it's fine. And it's like but then it's like my name too and
But I didn't and be I didn't do anything and also be I did not hide anybody nor time anybody out
I just deleted some comments and I also said before I did it
That I was gonna be hiding some comments because
They were slanders I felt and so like but you said don't hide them anymore, so I won't but
I just gonna stick I just think I'm just in the future
Just not gonna be paying attention to your chat
But I will I will go on your panel if you'll have me still and talk to you, but
It's when there's people screaming at me and it's like and I'm not like aggressive
talker
And so sometimes I have to get aggressive when they're all yelling at me and saying untrue stuff, but I'm not saying anything wrong, okay?
I'll put the F in the way. Okay, got you.
Yeah, I understand. You can have a talk about it. And it's like, but I just want you to know I love you Paula.
So let's
understand that before anything and it's like look these people are trying to
put a rift and they have them for a while between us, okay?
Look, I really don't want us to be affected by these trolls.
Okay, so let me see if we can invite fast.
Oh my gosh, yeah, I'm gonna be deleting.
Yeah, okay, I'll actually leave this comment.
Yeah, electric dot, okay.
There you go.
I'll pin my link too.
I know it. I know she's coming up. It's me. Oh, oh, hello. Are you there? Hi. Hi. Hi. It's me. Okay. Hi, sweetheart. Hi
Sorry, I just I went for like a walk and then I came back and took a shower
Thank you. I guess slander too not only on my
But on your panel too, right? Right, but I
But I get cussed out they say I'm a bitch. I'm always
It was last night, but I'm telling you
No, that's two nights ago, and I told him to stop as soon as he was saying I said stop
Yeah, I mean it was like 48 hours ago. Yeah, but I know but I was like
But I was saying I told him to stop doing it and then how many times you come to stop doing it before you gave up
And he just continued with it
I don't care who gives a fuck. He called me a bitch and a conch and he says I'm an evil witch
And I'm trying to not be a good friend to you and all that you know all of it
Do you don't think it hurts me too? You don't think that's wonder I do you don't think it's like making me like you know
There's a purpose. The purpose was I was trying to
I get to his side or you know have him talk and they're talking and a lot of
Conversation was have that and I told him stop say that I said if you say it one more time
You're out. I don't want you to stop
I just let him say whatever but don't get so sensitive when people say the same shit on my panel like we have different
Like yeah last night. They were yelling at me again these like accusations like it's like thank you
I've been on your panel and last night like
Like not just even last night, you know Alex and all these like people. They've called me like the worst of the worst late
I literally have told me you want me to never come back. Is that like
No, I can't you think I agree with any of this, but the beta thing is like
Don't I don't remember a city. I remember city talking in a calm voice at least we were saying to see not yelling over you
Not letting you like interrupting not letting you not speak it on me calmly or telling you calmly that I'm a bitch and laughing
It's a tone that really makes a difference for you
We're going to have this conversation over and over.
All right, well, let me just tell you,
we can have this conversation or not.
It's always going to be the same thing.
Maybe I shouldn't come to your panel
or look in even your chat and you shouldn't do it either way.
I do love you so much.
I do love you.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I do love you, I love your presence.
I do love when I see you, but if it's going to be,
if you're going to get attacked or I'm going to get attacked
channel. Maybe it's best that I just kind of keep my distance, you know? Okay, well, because then
they win, then they win exactly what they wanted. Well, you know, this is what I keep telling you,
you were going around circles, I keep telling you, we're dealing with the same shit, like people
are going to say shit about you or me. Right, I understand, but they're saying, I'm calling animal
control on you. They're saying, I have shit over my wall, over my floor. You know people have said
on my panel and your panel that um I asked my chat that I should be 51 50 um they put my
they've called like listen I've been a tour at all you're a managing mod and I said you have and
even though you say I shouldn't like you know touch your chat at all and it's like whatever I you
can do whatever I didn't unmod you you were taking you were coming out sherry it was like a really
I didn't time her up sweetheart. I did not time anybody out. I just deleted comment. I did not time anybody. I swear
Well, you're definitely above her that you took that out and it really pissed her off to a point where she called me and like
What the fuck I just said what you said like he said like
She said like I just repeated what he said that you know, I don't want to repeat it's not a big deal
You know, I mean
But I was, you know, I was, I just saw.
I really don't know how to like come to a resolution.
I don't really think we're going to get anywhere because I feel like each time I go live, I'm going to get blamed.
And let them win. Let them win.
And it's like, I know that you're comfortable.
What do you mean let them win?
Because it's like, what? You're probably...
I don't let anybody win.
Literally, your entire chat was fucking trollin' me.
My entire chat.
130 people, like, 160 people
are just talking to me.
Everybody that was talking.
Thank you. That's not fucking true.
Yes, it is. I was there. I was there. I'm watching. I wasn't thinking if there was like a whole chat going on for you
Oh, that there's something wrong. That's not what happens
You look at like five or two people and like a bunch of people
Okay, so what am I supposed to do?
I'm not saying you're supposed to do anything, but it seems like you know
Rather than like and you didn't defend me and I said that and I try to defend you better
It's like you think that I'm like I don't want you to defend me
But I just want to let you know like no matter what I honestly
100% like I will never ever go back on that till I see anything that's you know
Which I would never ever see. I think you take really good care of your cats. I love your cats
I love your relationship with cat your cats. I think they're very healthy
You treat them so sweetly and it really hurts me
to every fucking like every degree that anybody would turn to even like
Jeopardize your relationship with your castle. That's not me. Okay?
That's not what I believe in.
Maybe we just agree with the whole thing, but...
I know, yeah.
And I know you were defending, and you said that, and it's like, I really appreciate that.
And I will say, I don't agree with some of the things that are said, or like all, most, like any negative thing I don't agree with.
And it's like, and I think people are just trying to put a rip between us.
And so it's like, if we like, that's why I keep going to your show, even though I know it's going to be bad sometimes.
But I go with like a good intention.
trying I've been trying to like my do my best like I was trying to make up with a lot of people
there's people that are mad over stuff that happens they don't know because you know what
there's certain people I'm not going to make up with like on your panel on my panel you know
remember like there are some people I just don't mesh with like at some point I found out J-Dog
and I just don't mesh you know there are certain people like you know I'm just saying like we can't
Some of your mods hate me, some of your mods hate me.
Okay, I don't think any of my mods are disrespectful to you,
but some of your mods go after me and stuff like that,
but I'm not gonna say anything,
but I'm gonna say, like I was telling somebody I shared,
like, be and I have an understanding that it's like.
she does her thing I do my thing we're gonna have different people that she
likes that I don't like and if they're the people that I like that she doesn't
like I don't tell my mom to go off to you I just have different types of moths we
I'm a lot more open you know and just do it I don't have a discord we don't talk
behind the scenes I don't even know what happens
it just all happens and I do unmod a lot of my mods that I think that they're disappointing me
you see that how about the person this morning that would say Psyche unalived himself Psyche's
hanging from the raptors and you're like what and then it's like you kind of we're almost laughing
Psyche people say I um did a lot of things too they say I killed this person and I killed the
I'm an uncle effort and I don't know that and I also want I also want you to be able to have free reign as a mod
Just to the channel whatever here DJ lectures here. Thank you
I don't want them to like as long as they're not doxing or like saying like I mean I just it's like
The more you tell them not to do it like beta stop telling beta. She's like an uncle effort
They're gonna do it more, but I'm just saying it's like you're a monetized channel. I'm not
Hi, I just want to mediate a little bit because you guys are not focusing on solutions. You're focusing on complaints and I don't think it's being productive.
So, like, what would you prefer the other person does when you because if you want to stay in contact and go on each other's panels.
What would you prefer that the other person does when you are being attacked on panel beta ignore.
Ignore it
Um, if it's if it's like something that I think it should be defended you best your ass
I'm gonna fucking defend it
So when people say that say he's not taking care of his cat and this is like cat
He's got this on his couch. I'm like, no that's fucking cabinet. No, but if
But if people are attacking you beta
On his
You know what my cats are my family the same way
if he's gonna he should actually defend me too and he does when he comes to my family and friends
and that's it you know and my cat okay so he does defend you you're saying yeah what are what are
you upset about what are you guys well I'm not upset about anything psyche is upset I've gotta
I went live and um, he was upset at me, so I don't know why you're saying
What are we upset about let's like he say how he feels
Okay, I'll leave so you can talk to psyche then no, no, I want
You're telling me what am I is my issue. I'm here to like be there for psyche
today and we're discussing it and we are friends and you know what um same way he came on my panel
he knows what happened okay one of like it doesn't it's like me taking you out as like one of my
fucking like people i trust one of my mods and be like you know what i'm gonna time dj electric
have i ever timed you out dj electric yes i have yep really yeah yep proof of that
I didn't screenshot it or anything because I thought I was fake or something, but it was really me
I never fucking it was basically you coming under a fucking different name and I said, I don't know if it's fucking real DJ
Electra and you came on the panel
Yeah, yeah, but you did time me out. That's all I said. I'm saying
You know, but I just was trying to mediate so you could talk and then psyche could talk and you guys could eat
Okay, do you tell a show how many people do you time out and I'll thank you such
Nobody not not very often unless you do I do I say something. Do I ever time anybody out and fucking psyche strong?
No, you observe recently recently or ever and I don't ever fucking touch fucking psyches shot
Recently or I don't ever fucking touch fucking psyches shot. I'll come up and I'll be like
Can I like time that person out only happened once or twice?
Like going after my family
You don't have to ask me that you can just do it, you know, I trust you I will ask
Yeah, no, we don't have to be I want you guys so why are you time in a sherry that I've known for six fucking years and what she
She's my mom
You just timed her out. I didn't time her. I swear. I did not time anybody. I just deleted comments
I did not time anybody. I swear to God in fact, but I was like
I wasn't able to like pick out some of the comments I wanted to that mods were safe
Thank you. You already you already you did say that you time share you out sure
No, I said I did not I swear to god beat it. I've all I've said is okay. Believe in her comments. What does she say? What does she say?
I don't remember because a lot of people were saying things and so I don't remember exactly her exact comment
I just look at the comments and the comments that were laying you know
There's things that she says to you are the same thing that she would say to me beta
You're drinking too much beta. Go to sleep. I don't know her beta. You know, you don't know her. That's she's my mom
There's the reason she's my mom
You took out you deleted her comment because she said that you should get your cats vaccinated
Well, I don't remember it exactly or that's what she said. She said don't let your couch out and get them vaccinated and that's that
She didn't say anything nasty about you. Well, I didn't time her out either. It's like did you delete her?
No, I did the comment the comments. Yeah
Being a liar, right? I can't send you
Okay, show me why I timed out time throughout not just a little bit comment I timed out
So we were timed out her. Okay. I want to find that find that where I timed her out. Let's find that, please
Sherry, I did not time anybody out. I swear to God. I did not time one person
You already came on my panel and you said you were sorry about doing yet
No, I said if I if I deleted a comment that was like not
I didn't time anybody out. Okay. I did not time or hide anybody
I said I'm gonna delete some comment and I said you can on mommy if you if you want because I said
I mean I hang up right now and I'm gonna have to delete some comments in your chat
And I did and I was not dessert
It was several people because I was just being like it was just so many people and it's like maybe sometimes one person will
be saying something to you and something like there's like 20 all going after me and just being
denigrating and it's like it's like a little I know that I'm not saying it's worse or better or
anything I'm saying I you can have free reign if someone bothers you with any comment I trust you
okay I give you I trust you you don't have to ask and I won't care because there's just a comment
in a chat like at the end of the day and it's like even if you were to hide somebody
or time them out, it's not a big deal
cause I can always like unhide people and stuff.
So I bet, I trust you to make the decision
and I will, whatever you want, okay,
but it's your chat, right?
And whatever you want, I will follow your rules.
But you said, so you said don't hide people
or time people out and I didn't.
I just deleted some comments that I felt were slanderous
and a lot of, and I told you, go read the comments
that I give you so you can still see everyone
that I deleted and you can decide if it was.
Fair or not, and you can unhide the comment too,
but I didn't hide anybody.
I didn't hide or tag anybody out,
just deleted some comments, okay?
So that's it.
I mean, and maybe I deleted a few,
but there was a lot of stuff being said
that I felt was lies or unfair or just like,
like just bullying too.
And so-
Did she leave?
Oh yeah, she did.
But yeah, and it's hard, and I love her so much,
You know four months ago something he said and it's like it's just like never been able to resolve it
It's always the same the same thing over and over and over with like that and it's like I feel like I don't know
I wish it's like a deep breath deep breath just remember that what these people say online is not reality
It's not true, and it doesn't matter
You got to let it go
Because it's affecting you
Yeah, I mean, if you want to stay online and create content and have your channel and go on other people's channels
You got to just let it go. It's not real and it's like and sherry and beep beep, you know, it's like, you know, I
Feel I just don't appreciate how you're talking to me and like it's just like and you don't need to
Don't give me saying this to me. And so I just don't feel like dealing with you guys today. No on your own channel
On your own channel, you definitely should go ahead and delete these people and hide them. I agree. They're trolls
I think someone unleashed a fucking herd of trolls on you this morning, especially
That's hard. I mean, it's like and I'm trying to
Be calm and know rational about it, but I think on other people's channels. Maybe
You don't delete the comments. Just leave them and maybe just leave that that I will yeah area
Because that's a good thing about online is you can always leave right a certain situation and you don't have to stay there
Yeah, this morning they don't have to listen to that crap and once you leave they stop usually, you know, right?
No, but I wasn't okay. So lecture. I was there when nobody knew I was there and
People had my name Psyche's floor. They had their car. I know Psyche you can't correct. Yeah, you can't correct the record
You can't correct the record online. It's never gonna happen. Stop. It's just an endless cycle. If you keep trying they keep trolling
Just give up on it. I
That's not being weak that's being strong that's saying these people are idiots
They're talking shit, and it doesn't matter because it's not true. You know, it's not true
You know
It's easier said than done, but
Just getting wrapped up in it is the worst. I know it's
You know how much it hurts me it hurts me
It's uh, but it's fine. It's fine. Why are you letting them hurt you? Why because their words don't mean anything
Right, but this is like because people
Believe some of these people and it's like and they're pushing the people that matter will not believe them
The people that matter will never believe them. You think I believe a word of what those trolls say no
They're idiots. They are dumb. They don't even have a good
Any good arguments or anything good to say they have nothing going for them. They're losers in some basement in their mommy's house
You know some of them are probably like 20 years old 22 years old
And you're gonna argue back with them to just block them move on
You have to yeah, I will
otherwise
You're just spinning your wheels and
you know
like wasting your your own energy I know and it's like it's so hard with
panels to begin with but and it's also some of these communities I had such a
great time on like you know Alex mayors chat there is never never a problem in
her to not one person they say it's like so nice and I know like some of these
communities I don't know it just like seems like I got I get so hated and it's
like it hurts that I get hated and I
I'm there for Bita and it's like and so when I'm just there trying to talk to Bita and have fun and like
and talk to some people on our panel and then all the panels is hacking me
Slandering and it's like and then it's like yeah, that's when you got to leave that situation psyche
Yeah, what's the point of staying except allowing them to hurt you?
You're allowing them to do it. You know that you realize that right?
right
I know well it's like I know it's like you're allowing them if you stay there. I know so I know I probably should not be there
I and I but that's and that hurts me because I don't want to I do love you know like and I want to
Support her and and it's like I guess but if I don't want to hurt her show, but it's like people are having fun
just like making me a
Disgusting monster then it's fine. It's fine. Sorry. Halo. I didn't mean you
about the basement. Sorry. Sorry about that. Okay. Oh, man. Yeah, I agree with that. Can't
please everyone. See what I mean? You just can't. But I like Halo. Sorry. I don't, I
didn't mean that about you. Yeah. Okay. So I just like, I just got a, I see that she's
Really bad. I can't have a my check. It's fine. It's fine if they want to play over there and stuff like that
And it's like I'll stay away and I'll even if I'm there maybe I'll stay out of stay out of the chat and not look at it anymore
Who's messing with me KZ?
Who isn't messing? I mean, it's like no who isn't messing with me a bunch of nobodies are messing with him
He doesn't even know who these people are. That's the thing
They are nobody important I never did I never did anything to these people and it's like they have no right
They don't know me that they can you know defending yourself again stop. Okay? Okay?
What they say does not have any reflection on you it does not matter you
Gotta get that through your head
I love your lecture. Thank you for like commenting. I love you too. Yeah. And it's like, and I'm okay. Like, I can, I'm glad it's not, I'm glad it's me and not somebody. I'm not that somebody else that couldn't take it as much as I can, because, you know, at least I can be strong. But, you know, it's like, I don't, I know it's, I feel bad for people that are going to meet the victims of some of these people. And it's like, I know this is some, I don't know, it's just not acceptable.
For my the more that we give them attention the more that they keep doing it to so it's like good just change the subject
It's fucking hot today. That's what I'm talking about. I think everyone's crazy because it's so damn hot this heatwave is crazy
Yeah, it's not even 11 yet, and it's what like 80
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I apologize, I wasn't paying attention to the screen. I'm sorry. I didn't hear is she back?
Come back. Come back. Come back.
You know, I'm not paying.
I won't. I won't.
Can I can I just pay attention to the chat
and if you just see that kind of like really horrible stuff said here,
I got you. Yeah, I'll just pay attention to chat.
You can come back up and I'll let you guys chat.
Yeah, thank you. I had to restart my, um, I don't know, my phone went to the one UI thingy and I have to restart it. Um, I feel like we were going a little bit somewhere, but I think we should talk maybe in private whenever you want. And, um, for now, I'll stay off your panel and your chat and maybe you should like.
you know because I don't want to you know it's sad it's sad it's sad well it's like
you're always welcome here in it but my chat loves you yeah and you're always welcome there you'll
be more there but I mean your your your your chat hates me your chat hates me your panel hates me
like everyone hates me it seems over there um I don't think that's true at all but that's what
your conclusion is there's a few you'll figure that out at the end you know okay yeah no I've already
figured it out I feel like me and you are talking and we're kind of going somewhere but then all
Yeah, well, yeah, then it's been all this stuff happened all the sudden DJ lecture I came in here and like she just like okay, like, you know, whatever
I mean, we can always talk a lot. Okay
She's trying to help she's trying to help
I I think you just you you're very easily um
You know
Yeah, it's it's really good. It's better for you to stay away from me
Okay, I'll stay I'll stay away from you then. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Bye. Bye
Yeah, so that's so basically the trolls win, you know, because it's like
Yeah, she's just gonna
She's just gonna take their side I guess all the time so it's sad it's sad because it's like I love her so much, but
Fine fine, and we do make progress and then it's like but I don't know guys
You can watch back the episode you can make your own conclusion whatever it's like
Yeah
Wow, well, you know
Be like that. Okay. It's like I'd love to have a great conversation
But it's like it's like it seems like I can't get anywhere. It's been the same broken record for months and months and months
It's like I'm there for her
I'm not there for like her chat or for people on her family. I'm there for her and
You know, she people love her here, but she don't whatever I she's always welcome
I bet she's being difficult and it's being too difficult for me to like
To handle it so I mean because really it's like if you do how much I
Didn't care for then I don't know but I guess now I'm just like some
Yeah, she can just go ahead and have her chat
Let me
Yeah, it's me. Yeah, maybe right, okay
I well my cats are my cats are my babies. It's like, you know, it's like but
As a friend, I consider her my best friend, but she's already made it clear that she doesn't, so...
I'll give up. I kept trying to fix things. I give up.
But I was really trying to have a good show today too, you know? And it's like...
Why are they I don't know out there because it's like it because it hurts me and they just want to hurt me, okay?
They just want to hurt me
Yeah, I don't really even want to repeat some of the stuff that I saw this morning, but
it was cruelty and it's like yeah people might be like you know she's a
from she knows some of these trolls or whatever like you know and so it's like
you know I don't know some of these friends with some of them one day and
then the next day so but they're consistently hating me though and it's
like and I know people here love her and stuff like that and I'm so I'm sorry
Seem to be able to work things out. I don't know what's wrong
But I'm not gonna play a victim or anything just
Basically she's letting them win
Right, and it's like and they're her friends is in the first place and so whatever choose choose all that choose all that
But I certainly
How did you do it?
I know it's hard, it is hard breaking, tree frog, it's sad, it is sad.
I'm a little bit I don't want I don't want I don't want to get down I was having such a good day
I was I'm like I was like I premiered my video and I was having a good chat and then it's like
It just went off I don't know it just went off the rails yet and I wasn't trying to blame her or
anything I was like I understand I was like she doesn't have to even defend me she could she was
I feel like sometimes she just agrees with them, you know, about a lot of themselves and you know,
and that's what really hurts because I see, I look at her very highly. I look at her,
like you can go to my, go to my post and just, do you want to see what I feel about her? It's
like the, you know, the Empress is just like a divine feminine, like this is like
She'd rather be beautiful to everybody else and
as we're last seen on August 21st, 2025.
And Berler.
Yeah, I mean, it is different because I am a business
and maybe it's like not conducive for me to be
in some of, like around some of these communities
as a monetized person because
then it's like also my business is like my baby my cats are my babies my I care
about people here my friends I try I do you try I don't want to be sound like
why you play I don't want to be in a low energy chip I want to be I want to be a
Like I'm always still I'm always wrong. I'm always
like if I fall and
I'm a joke and
and it's like
The worst part is like thinking like your best friend
Breeze with that I don't look like an explainer, but I don't I don't want to talk
I'm sorry guys, I don't want to bring any video down or anything like that, so I guess I'll wrap it up.
And I just wanted to do my show and have fun.
Wow, it's really sad. It is heartbreaking and it's like difficult.
You really knew how much I love people.
I wish some and I know I know you guys care but there are people that like love me
it's okay but
okay I'm just gonna go because I don't want to be accused of like
crying or anything and I'm sure next time I look at the chat it's gonna be
it's what I don't know it's really hard and if you knew how if you knew how much it was hurting
It's basically, I'm a joke, I'm a monster.
That's just common perception, common knowledge now.
Whatever, the common, just so many people are saying it,
it must be true.
There's new people that I've met that are like,
oh my gosh, well this is, I mean if this person,
he must be like so terrible if it is.
His mods are saying stuff about him, and his friends think about it, but it must be true, right?
I don't know. There seems to be something else, like something...
I don't know, maybe...
The worst thing would be if I started to take it to heart, and I really don't want to, but it's hard.
We love, um, trying to, but I hope you have a good day guys. Sorry, sorry it went off the rails again.
And I don't want to like, stay here and like,
I'm sort of crying or something so I'm just gonna say I love you and have a good day and you know.
I need to take a deep breath, meditate.
Maybe I will take a walk or something like that,
but again, I'm gonna feel misunderstood.
I feel ganged up on,
which is not just ganged up on,
like just ganged up on by like a mob.
Like it's like, not just like,
because it's like, yeah, one person's saying B-I-T-C-H.
Few time you ever see and I had explained I was like I want him to get his story and you know, so I will let people talk
And I said stops I told him stop saying it and eventually I didn't kick him off down so
But it's like
It's just like so many people like it's just like so many it's like if you guys would see the chat there even when I'm not there
It's just I'm a laughing stock
Hold on take out
I'm sorry if I'm not reading this chat right now guys. It's a little hard to do right now. Hold on.
Hi Arthur.
Hello. Hello. Hey what's up dude. So it's like real quick I have this um crazy theory. Um yeah.
She's been talking a lot about your donos right? She's been talking about your donos and then she's
like well I don't care about the money but
You know, thanks to me. You know, you're getting donations. She's been saying a lot of that as of late, right?
I've heard some things along that line. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna say anything about like, you know, I just I don't I don't know
I don't know her
Yeah, I have this crazy theory
I have this crazy theory you haven't been going live as you used to as much you used to go live like every day all day
Right. I have this crazy theory that she's purposely triggering you
To like end streams so you don't get donations as much as you used to
Only you know that you probably hasn't haven't made as much doughnose this month as much as last month
No, every yeah, my donators get attacked
I'm having this crazy theory she's jealous of your success bro
Well, I don't I mean she doesn't she's not even monetized and I didn't think she cared that much about that kind of stuff
For someone who doesn't care. She's always bringing it up though. Hey, it's me. It's definitely me. Hi. Hi. Oh my god
You better not give up on what you're doing. Okay. Don't you dare?
To the chat this lady put control is daughter on a stripping pole are you right here are you right here i'm on i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm
Don't give up you have a good following you have a little drama right now the only reason I even know that there's anything going on it's got someone down to me about it was like there's a drama tell him not to quit so i'm telling you don't matter what people are going to try to chase you off they're going to try to make you doubt yourself make you feel bad especially if you're doing something that they're not capable of doing.
You have a certain gift. I'm not just saying that I really feel that about you and when you do there's you know
Whenever you're basically of the light or good
The opposite is gonna be like oh you think you're gonna do something
I don't think so I'm gonna hold credit oppress you or suppress you and hold you down and all this kind of mess
you have to
Kick ass and take names
And you know what, it's like, you always make,
you always like make me feel better.
It's like, you're just because I think you see me.
Like you, like, I feel like,
I feel like a lot of people don't see me
and that's a lonely feeling sometimes.
And it's like, but, you know, and I know,
and I see, you know, you too,
and I know you've been through a lot, you know,
a lot of similar things.
And it's like,
Well people like to say I'm a doxer, okay?
Do you know that I'm one of the most dox people that there's ever been in the United States from when I?
I think I told you when we had our long conversation the other night when I was active in the entertainment industry
Something happened to where everyone's personal information came out and I, I mean, my parents found out I was doing things that they didn't know I was doing. I was devastated. I was thinking life is over. But then I decided, you know, I don't want life to be over. I just have to come up with a new norm and I did.
I think I probably took things a little further than most would.
It in a way it made me stronger in a way I learned some hard lessons, but at the same time what you're going through
from my perspective is and I'm not diminishing what you're going through but
It could be so much worse
what you really are going to have to do is just um
tightenship people that you absolutely know are negative for you cut them out
your life and it's hard to do that but you can do that
yes because
My show was not, like, my intention was not to have a big drama show all the time, but
I was really, like, discouraged, I feel, and maybe I should just, like, you know, I need
to, like, man up and say, I control the show, I control the ship, but I was very much discouraged
from even timing out or hiding anybody, like, it was, like, everybody would go into a kind
of an uproar when I would do that, and I was like, whoa, and so, and so, and so, and I
by other people. I need to get to that north node, Leo energy instead of being in my lower self,
where I just kind of blend into the crowd and become another like, you know, face on my own
show. I need to, I need to man up and take control of the show. And it's like, I really need to.
And it's like, and if it means not
Putting myself out there on other shows and just focusing on this one
But I mean, but I had a great I had a great time on your show. It just showed me
Thank you. I do I do come with a little bit of a mini agenda. Okay
Maybe once a week
You could come on my panel and we'll talk about something metaphysical or paranormal or spiritual or whatever it can we can split it up to where it's a brief discussion then we do a brief recap then we let some people come on the panel as long as they can conduct themselves appropriately it'll be my panel so i'll be a hard ass but you'll be my special guest and maybe we could do that.
Once a week for the next three weeks as a trial run, you know, you can promote your show and that way it's a little bit more of a controlled environment and i think a lot of other people would want you on their show in a similar format but you got a demand that things are under control and don't get out of control so if you want to do that i'll figure out a day and a time and.
Yeah, I absolutely love that because I just had the best time talking to you and then last night. I was you know
I was I was talking about you know ancient Roman history and stuff like that with you know
It's with gaudy and stuff and
Having gotten gaudy too like I thought another side of it when he was on your show with us and
It's like, now I'm getting along a lot better with him.
I even made up with some other people
I was having problems with.
And so, I would absolutely love that.
And I just thank you with like, I really, you know.
I like you a lot, I really do.
I think that you are like a breath of fresh air.
The communities that are familiar with you right now,
they're not ready for you.
Okay, they're just not you're a little bit more sophisticated than what they're used
to and you are sensitive and being that you are sensitive, you do have to properly guard
yourself because when these people, when they smell blood, they're like sharks, okay?
I think it feels like I'm being eaten by sharks literally. It feels like I'm just like it coming from all directions and Terry and I can't even
Like address one thing without the other thing and it's so it's difficult for me. I'm not that
Assertive sometimes and it's like I like to be calm and I don't like to yell. I hate yelling. I don't like to
have to like
try to like
Especially when people they won't let me talk sometimes and it's like I can't even get it a word and it's really frustrating
because I'm trying to
Get along. I'm trying to
You know be a positive force and try to help people even negative people. I really wanted to help people so well
Don't help negative people
You know you're gonna end up hating me because I'm gonna tell you straight up
Don't don't why are you gonna help someone who's gonna tear you down help people only who builds you up?
That's I think maybe your spiritual lesson of the day is that
You don't have to help or be kind to people who are not going to reciprocate.
It's not right.
Some people will see that quality within you and be like, oh, here's somebody that I can exploit and take advantage of.
You don't want to be that person, especially right now, because you are building.
I've taken a look at your online presence.
You've done a great job as far as what you've built for yourself so far, in my opinion.
I think that you are going to have to...
Create more so of a format for your show and stick with it for now. That way it creates a little bit more routine and consistency for yourself and people who are troublemakers don't tend to like routine and consistency.
So eventually they'll drop off from bothering you but the people who are bothering you you know you just kind of make it clear look.
maybe you're gonna say I'm a certain way for this,
but you're blocked, you're banned, you're out of here,
whatever you gotta do.
And the right people who genuinely wanna spend time
with you online, they're gonna be there.
But the wrong people they're just going to see up. I can't do anything with this person and they're going to move on
But you're going to ultimately create your own community
You're you don't have to worry about
Other people's communities liking you or not because the internet is infinite. You're gonna have people from other
countries, you know, who want to hear what you have. I mean, you're providing an amazing service.
You're creating an environment to where
You're educating but you're also, you know, sometimes you're doing your free readings for people
Readings are expensive. I don't think people understand how expensive high-quality readings actually are
So what's like he is giving you is a tremendous gift
And he probably won't be able to constantly do that because he's gonna have so many people coming at him with money
That he's not gonna have time for you anymore
So some of you need to appreciate him while you can
And thank you always the, you know, you help me see the light, you know, and you are, and speaking of breath of fresh air, like you are certainly a breath of fresh air and, you know, you're amazing and, you know, I'm just blessed to know you.
Blessed to be your presence, you know, you're awesome.
Well, I'm blessed to have come across you also.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna figure out a day in time.
that we can consistently do a segment, well not a segment, it's going to be a whole stream
over on my channel or whatever. I'll pick out some topics that way you know in advance.
You can even pick the topics because I always have like a million things on my mind. So I'll
come up with like seven or eight and you narrow it down to three. We'll do one topic per show.
And I think that'll be a good way to introduce you to some people that are more so on my side.
And I think that'll make you feel a little bit better.
Thank you. I think so too. And I really look forward to that immensely.
Yeah, it'll be cool.
And thank you. Thank you.
Thank you for being my friend, you know, thank you for no problem. No problem
Well, let me let you go. I gotta get on with my day
I just wanted to come here into the person who didn't like me before guess what whoever you are
I don't like you either. So suck it. All right
You
people like Alex and there's so many people in the chat too um that are kind and have my back
and love me and I'm sorry if I focused on the negative too much but thank you okay I really do
appreciate guys and I love you okay and uh yeah I'm gonna light some incense I'm gonna light some
Like I have a lot of the evil eye stuff right now, and so maybe I'll get out my deck
I'll get out of that because you know this is a tarot show right and it's like you know
I love tarot and sometimes the reason I don't do as much is because I feel like
Not a lot of people like
You know are asking or fishing and you know I I
Know I know I'm good. Okay. I know I'm good and it's like
I feel like some people have denigrated terror a little bit, and I feel like you need to make it more a part of the show.
And also, yeah, I gotta get, sometimes I have a little bit of a way too free of a format.
I'd love to map out a format that works.
That's entertaining and that like I had a person in the chat last night
She's this woman from South Africa as she was new and she was like hey, she's like I like you
I really like you and
She stayed with me until the end of the show and she's you know, she watched the video and she is like
Some of my some of the AI stuff I did she was in the person was like wow
This person it was just it was just cool. It was like
Wow, I'm not getting it. Hey, baby
You've been at the door now. I'm at the door. Come on, babe
Hey tricks. Come on. You're okay, babe. What are you meowing at? I'm at the door
I don't know. Are you good? Are you good, babe?
Yeah, so I have this haters expose
And I'm sorry. It's the ones that beat us in tears. I'm I hope she's not in tears
You know, I love beta like I really really love beta and it's like if it's a misunderstanding and stuff like
Misunderstandings can be worked out like it's a different story when we're talking one on one
It really is and so it's like but it's so different when there's other people involved
And it's like I that's why I feel it's like if it was just between the relationship was like so tight
It was like hey, no one's gonna get to us. We're we're tight. We're but it's like, you know
How subided falls and it's like I feel like people have been trying to split us apart and
Let's just see that
How much these people hate me? It's like I think that 90% of people in this chat, you know love her and it's like
And I think 90% of people in her chat hate me, right?
And it's like, and so it's a little bit of a misunderstanding.
I have no ill feelings or will.
It's just, it's sad.
I'll pull some of these haters exposed cards
and this will be.
It might relate to you might relate to me. We'll see what comes out in this deck
It'll also maybe have some good advice of some remedies
Okay, I know I'm gonna be looking for some kind of power symbol talisman
To maybe put some in good intention energy and shoe and maybe protect protect me a little bit and you know
And I'm sorry I'm not looking at the chat that much guys. Let me let me have a look at the chat
Yeah, I'm gonna light some incense too. This is some this is called witches brew. Okay. This is a really sweet smelling
Great incense. Okay, so there's a witches brew and you know, I'm gonna light this by the way. I have
respect for people all you know all traditions and I've studied all
traditions and
And not necessarily, you know, choose one over the other.
I think there's great stuff in all of them, okay?
But I'm not like saying, oh, wishes or, you know,
I think anybody can be, it's like, it's about the person.
It's not necessarily the beliefs of the person, right?
And so, okay, so let's light some of this up.
Take a deep breath, you know, open my curtains maybe, okay?
Get some fresh air in here and light this incense.
Look at my little pyramid and hey, maybe we'll get some good messages, okay?
Okay, so that's lit.
It's lit.
Okay, I'll put it right there.
I mean, open my curtains.
light in here, beautiful day here, a little bit more.
Hey, man, come on up here.
Come on up here, babe, please.
Are you, yeah, I'm upset, so you're upset,
what, that how it goes?
I don't know if you could tell I'm upset, baby.
You're my little baby, you're my little baby, baby, baby.
Okay.
Be the, and I hope we can talk,
Be the, and talk one-on-one, and hopefully
working this out.
Maybe this, maybe it's just,
I think it's other people getting in the way. Okay. I'm sorry, and I'm sorry if you're hurt. Okay. I don't want to hurt you
Okay
You don't think she's okay. I know I know I know I know I know I know she does and it's like and I'm not saying yeah
I don't think she's envious either. I mean, it's like but at the same time, um, you know people like
The comment has been made. Oh, I mean, you know, I well the comments are made. I made you first of all, I
Basically I
I had
I've had help from some people like a lot of people
Especially my friend from the Philippines chono and I started before before I met me
I had I had at least a thousand subscribers
So and I work really hard too on going to a lot of different communities and panels and
Stuff like that and she did help immensely, you know, I guess and so many people have helped me and then yeah
And she she in a big way. It's helped me a lot. I'm so appreciative
I met wonderful people like Alexandra through her and I've introduced her to wonderful people. Okay
J-Dogs here. Let's bring up J-Dog
Yo, what's up psyche? How you doing, man?
Good, how are you doing chilling chilling man, dude? I'm sorry to see all the drama that's going on between you and Vita
Yeah, me too. I'm I'm really
Regretful of it and a little bit
Mystified because I would hope that we would be able to because we have good coffee. We have great conversations
Wow, what we do and it's like that it seems like
When other people get involved
It changes things in a negative way, and I hate that and maybe it is me
I don't know going over there and no
Don't blame yourself dude. It's just the trolls honestly
The trolls, you know why because they know that they're gonna get on your nerves when you when you go over there
They know that they're gonna fuck with you
So they do it on purpose because they like this drama. They like to have all this
Comotion they like seeing you and beat a fight. They like seeing me personally. I wish you guys wouldn't have fight no more. I wish
You know, she wasn't I hate it. So do I I know I don't like I said
I might not get along with beat up personally, but that has nothing to do with your guys a relationship
you know, you guys are like this you guys were tight and
You know, she flipped the script on you and then she's trying to blame DJ Electron. I'm like whoa
Where did that come from all she give us just come in and try to be nice
Yeah, I mean she was she was trying to help mediate like and a really good intention like didn't come in here
Say anything at all negative to her, okay?
Like and so I just don't I'm kind of don't understand
KZ is this KZ hold on
Hold on I'll put my banner up and just I'll get you up here. Oh, hello. Hi. Hey
Okay, hey, what's up?
All right, all right, all right, of course Jada is up here. He's always got to be like me
Well, he was you know, he was here first
Well, I was you you had seen me back stage earlier. I was waiting my time to get up, right?
Yeah, I was just I was having a talk a one-on-one talk with the Dallas Andrew
But you know and I you know have to
kind of monitoring my panel in a certain way but you know I'm happy to have you
here when you know I have more of the open panel going on and so so what's
up bro thanks for being there she's she honestly I'll tell you the truth dude
Bita has a serious serious serious substance abuse problem I'm not trying
to bash her or nothing like that I'm not bashing anybody we all have our
deemings I have my deemings everybody has their own deemings
You know, but yeah
She needs to lay off though off the alcohol dude like she's the alcohol takes over her and just turns her into a
Monster and as she just bikes every hand that beaks her
That's the worst part like everybody who's trying to like say hey
How are you doing like if you're trying to shake her hand she'll bite your hand even though you guys were cool yesterday
And I'm like what the fuck
I know it's like the energy changes and it's like and it is I feel other people you know
It's like and it's like you know, it's like it's fine and it's like like I said
Like, for example, I talked to somebody yesterday.
I don't know if they want me to talk about their name yet, but there's somebody that
used to be on the show a lot, and I had a great affection for it, and that had an affection
for me.
And, I guess, because of the, no, it's a female, but because of this person, because of something
You know they felt that
I don't know something that they felt like
Things were getting in the way where I was being controlled by somebody and they just ended up starting to not like me
We yet we ended up you know having it falling out and then I invited them back to the show yesterday
They're like are you like do you know what you do you know like?
You're talking do you know that you know you want me back on this show? I was like yes
I was like I don't even remember why we're fighting and and then
You know there and actually there's we still have fiction for each other and the person does want to come back
I think this person will come back once they see that the the channel
You've gotten control the chat and channel again, and it's the way you want it. I'm sure these people will all come back
I hope so
Yeah, and I can't I guys in the past few days. I really have been wanting to
If I did something wrong
Guys, I want to like you know, do anything wrong psyche
You can do shit bro and all honesty bro everybody here. We're seeing everything like in black and white
I'm being I'm trying to be non-bias as I can but sometimes it's hard, but especially when I see
the other party doing stuff to the other person and the other one doing it.
I missed all this. I just came out.
No, dude, we don't went crazy on Psyche yesterday, bro.
Her, Sandman, Kiss My Cheeks went on Psyche. It was wild, bro.
Oh, this happened all of a sudden?
What happened?
on her channel. Yeah, on her chat. And it was like, it was a lot, it was a lot of people, it was a lot of people. And it's like, and then, I mean, Sandman was like saying, hey, let him talk, let him talk. It was basically, Heldo was basically going after me and part of that.
Yeah, but although the bitch we always know although all no honestly all those gifts. Well, I'm not gonna dox anybody
I'll do is just wait
Yeah
Which I have no idea what I have no idea why he's these content. It's probably just content. He sees content
You know, you know what the part is like I'm gonna tell you the truth, bro
I'm gonna swear to God tell you the swear to God truth. Well Arthur was saying earlier
I a hundred percent believe Vita is jealous of your success as much as she says that she's not about the money and
This this and that that's all she talks about with you
Like if you really think about it a lot of the arguments are oh all psyche cares about his money and donations and his brand and his logo
And his name and don't say this don't I think you both
your ears and
Pushing different narratives and trying to get drama
Yeah, I think that's the thing. It's like I wanted to stay united because it's like guys like we have a one-on-one
We are we are most of the time pretty good. There's been times
We know she's gone off on me a little bit one-on-one and and I maybe yelled back to and you know
There's been some stuff said to her that I do not like on the show and maybe I did not defend her
I should have but I also
came with the feeling that she has more of a longer relationship with some of these people
and a different relationship and that I don't understand and it's like, and so, you know, so...
Um guys, I do want to get out put Alexander's channel up so you can all subscribe to her
I'm just gonna grab that from
From I mean you got the link from my board real quick. Yeah, I think he me and posted it in chat, too
Oh, thank you. He man. Thank you. Yeah, put it up there
Okay, I appreciate you human. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. Okay
Yeah, I'll put down these cars for now, you know, I want I want to work things out. I don't know what I don't know
What it is. I don't know but it's the alcohol, bro
It's the alcohol if she's skate away from that fucking alcohol
But she she gets drunk she she on that drink ring bro, and when she gets on her drink drink, it's like
There ain't no coming back. There ain't no talking sense. It's like when she's on her drink, bro
It's like talking to a brick wall. You're not gonna get through to her no matter
It could be a child in the street trying to talk to her ask
You know, it's not serious. Yeah. Well, there could be somebody in the street saying where's my lost parent and she will yell at that kid
Like that's how that's how much the alcohol has control over her man
Like and I and I didn't drink last night, you know, yeah, you were normal you were sober last night
I've taken a lot of, I've drinking a lot less lately and, and you know, I remember I used to drink like every night and get drunk and pass out like every night and stuff like that.
And I was just, the show was a party at one point.
But, you know, as it gets more and more serious, it's like I'm wanting to perform better.
I'm actually like I've improved a lot like because I used to just stream all day and really neglect my maybe
my personal hygiene my health and
You know and plus drinking like every night and stuff. I would I would do that and
But I'm getting a little bit more
Wanting to be in control and stuff like that. So the fact that it's like now people are coming up with oh, I'm so dirty
It's like guys. I'm you're I've been here every day except for two days this year
I think they want to keep you locked in that way that you were you know, exactly
Exactly. Yeah, and I'm I'm about changing and I believe either and everything we can all change for the better
Right and and also, you know
They say about like psychopaths and stuff like that and narcissists that you can't win against them
And I'm saying that there are a lot of those kind of people around
Absolutely, yeah, it's pointless to argue with a narcissist. Yeah, do things that and they'll go places
I won't go. I'm not gonna like be cool. I wouldn't I wouldn't do
What's done to me to my worst enemy, okay?
I would not I would not say the things that have been said my worst enemy
First of all, even if they were in some kind of fault,
it's not my business to,
I'm just not gonna go attacking people.
I wanna help people.
Okay, let me ask you this, Psyche.
How come she gets pissed off when people say shit about her in your chat and then she wants you to defend people defend her in your chat
But then people can say whatever they want about you in her chat. She's left. Oh, well, I didn't know psyche or oh
I think that's just absurd. How can you yeah somewhere to in chat like you can't control the chat like that?
Oh, no, but I'm exactly I don't understand why she says that cuz psyche
I don't I don't get that and then once somebody says it people in chat are gonna
go and make that happen even more so.
Yep, they're going to get absolutely.
I see that, I see that, and it's like, and that's what I would say, I mean, that's what
I, that's the point I'm trying to say is like, okay, well, yeah, there's a time like that
she got, they don't, Arthur said something terrible, and I ended up deleting the show.
Okay, hold on.
It's her, excuse me.
Okay, well, and I don't want to be guys. It's like maybe if you might have to step down because I do want to have a good conversation
I don't know. I don't know
Well, I'd be to come up. Yeah
Okay, um, I cannot bring you up yet because the microphone is off. That's why can I bring you up? Let me see. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I'm sorry. I got it. I got it. I got it
Hello. Yeah, it's me. Okay. Okay. Hello. So you see like what your panel hosts are saying about me
Your mods are saying about me all this fucking shit and two people say things about you and you get upset
You play a victim a lot like you
Well, I'm having a conversation
I'm talking to psyche not you fucking j-dog. Just give me a sec. Just give me a sec guys
You're talking to KZ. I wasn't talking to your dumb ass beta
So it's my dumb ass, right, but psyche
Can I get a chance to talk ever goddamn
Please do please do my god. She's like an attention whore be to calm down. Thanks for letting me on last night though
I came at the same time as you did so I'll leave now you do this
Listen, you got great work beta. I appreciate you, but but psyche. What do you do for me? Nothing like I know I like it
I like to joke around a little bit, but I come on with my fucking music and you just kick me off
You're just a dick. Like what do you do for me? Nothing. It's okay. Yeah, don't take it
Don't take offense to a ghost though. He can't take offense to it
I'm waiting for him to answer. He's dumbfound look at him. He's just
Yeah, you don't do nothing for me dude, that's the whole point. That's why I came up
Okay, well, what you want? Okay, that's honest. You're playing we're about me in a negative way. No, they weren't
No, they weren't
Okay, you make me not even want to be an artist anymore, dude. You don't appreciate me
Fuck your control. Okay. I want to talk to Peter one second. Oh, she left. Okay. Yeah, she left you guys don't want to be here
I gotta go to
I mean see that didn't go very well and it's like in guys and I was gonna I don't know
It's like you're kind of like, you know call the name and it's like yeah. I mean it's like
I mean, I even have a chance to respond before she's responding to it. It's like I'm I'm very overwhelmed right now
I want to have a good conversation. Okay, so okay, can you come back, please?
You see KZ. She thought it was me. She thought it was me talking to her. That's how much she just takes me
She thought it was me talking to her. I didn't say I didn't even say anything
But then you call her I know
No, I called her name because she's a dumb ass like she can't decipher the voices like she don't know my voice
But it's not you're you're not calling her the news like it's not you doing it
No, but it's my fault though. It's my fault and so
Bro, she's gonna blame you if it rains, bro. She's gonna blame you for everything, bro
Don't don't even trip on that girl. She's crazy dude. She's crazy. I told you she was crazy
Well, I mean, it's like that's not I don't like to please just don't call her names
Okay, that's why I wasn't talking to her when she came up. I didn't say anything to her. I put myself on mute
Okay, well tell her to come up and then I'll leave tell her to come up and I'll bounce
Okay, but she's not going that way you could talk to her one-on-one
I can't, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
She's crazy cuz I had said that we didn't say anything negative, you know, I know I know KZ
I know what you said, bro. Yeah, but right away. She thinks it's me right away blame Jay dog
Hey dog Jay dog Jay dog. Jay dog did this Jay dog did that the fuck didn't Jay dog do I
Didn't want that to go like that and I was but I would have
I would have just said hey, let's do a one-on-one and it's like but I was like, okay
Yeah, no, we would have left me and KZ would have happily left bro
If you Abito wants to go one-on-one with you in no interference, bro
I will leave KZ. I'm sure KZ will leave too. Like let's just talk one-on-one by yourself. Yeah
Okay, so Stargazer, what are you saying?
Any man to talk to a woman the way you all have tonight or today, you're awful.
What are you talking about exactly as Stargazer?
I would like to hear more of what exactly you're talking about.
But it seems like, you know, and again, you are a mod, I don't...
Don't know if I said I don't know if I said anything. I don't know it's like they sometimes they talk to each other like that
I've seen her say something. I mean, I don't know
We all talk shit. You can't really take anything personal and I missed all that yesterday
So I thought I just thought I could be a good, you know, moderator with y'all too. That's why I asked me to come up
You will do don't have to come with a negativity bro like
She could just come talk to psyche one-on-one. No draw. Oh, you gotta go there. She's coming from two though because you know
I can't come I cannot get where a drunk
Substance abuse pillhead is coming
Guys, please I don't call her names. Please just don't call it. Just don't
Accusation please just this if you don't okay, okay? I'm sorry. Thank you my bad. Please. Please. It's just making things worse
It's making things worse. Okay. I'm sorry. I don't think she knows
Okay, I
Don't want to make things worse. I wanted to I want to heal things but
Don't know it's hard with it's like I can't control comes out of people's mouth. I'll just tell you this this KZ
The person who she gets them from I know
What you doing KZ
I'm just hanging out. I'm smoking on my vape getting young getting blazed up
Oh, yeah
You see Jimmy's last night, okay, no, I did Jimmy
Yeah, I missed it. I usually miss his late ones, you know, yeah
Well, because of again the yeah, you got struck and down, you know the stupid copyright those
Bullshit, it's me. Okay. It's 100% me
Now my comment in chat is I can't believe that some of you guys are talking to women the way that you are talking
I had listened to you all almost all night
Some of the things that were said you could have kept you trapped shut
And
People's feelings
Who are you addressing Stargazer? I'll love you. I'm me included. I am not dressing. Just one person
Yeah, that's what I'm asking. I'm asking but what did I say? What did I say?
You allow people to walk over you
Take up for you and then they get ran over also and then they're hurt because they're trying to take up for you
Okay, and I apologize. Okay. A lot of stuff is going on right now. Okay, so let me just take it. Let's get deep breath. Okay, so yeah, I'm
I'm trying to and you know, I've never came up here. You know, I've never said anything wrong to you
You know, I say the truth. You know, I sit back and I watch
Okay
You know this these relationships. I mean she's had a relationship with I think J-Dog for a lot longer than I've even known her and
They had a more it's like this. There's more complicated stuff. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know exactly
Like what is like I don't know what's going on sometimes or the people's relationships
Some people can talk to each other like that and it's like that's their relationship. I don't necessarily always
I understand that but when a person says do not say that to me
You're hurting my feelings and you keep on then what are you doing?
Well, were you there last night in her chat Stargazer and to see what happened to me yesterday on her show?
Yeah, what about the people are
Suck these nuts, bitch.
That's not, that's not, that's not, just call names, okay, let's just-
See, that's it, right there.
See, I'll say the B-word, and all of these men come running because they can't keep their mouths shut like a fucking medical equipment.
And you all can't disrespect me, you're disrespecting grown motherfuckers here, who the fuck is you, bitch?
Come up here. Come on up here. Just a second.
I don't want the fuckers.
We need your digs, bitch.
I'm not telling you to lie.
You're nothing, old lady.
You fucking 70-year-old bitch.
Pull them dentures out, bitch.
Suck my dick, bitch.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
No disrespect.
Let's talk rationally.
Fuck with you, dumb asshole.
You know, our bassies win it.
And I will not be back, Psyche.
I can't get you three more minutes.
Trying to talk to us like that.
Who the fuck is you, bitch?
Okay, okay, okay.
Suck my dick.
Chetty, man, Psyche.
Okay, I'm trying to hold on one thing. I need to get on me. Let me suck it on me. Okay. Thank you
Okay, well, who's coming up right now?
Okay, guys, I'm gonna I'm gonna take up J-Dog and KZ right now
And I'm gonna be on for a second. I want to talk without someone
So J-Dog, okay, so thank you. Okay, and I'm here. Oh, so here she is
I think it's me to make sure I'm sorry. I keep putting up the thing that okay
Why are you letting J-Dog talk to fucking?
Hold on. Hold on a minute, baby girl. Hold on. Hold on a minute.
Okay. Is that better? Okay. I think that's better. Yes. Okay. Okay.
My thing is the reason I came up is I have seen you and Bita.
Try to take up for each other. You all could be the bestest friends
and people would keep their nose out of your two businesses.
Yes, I agree.
I agree.
He doesn't give a shit stark either.
He just literally lit like fucking J-Doll saying that I do drugs
and he knows my fucking source.
I want him to say who my source is
because I don't fucking buy pills from fucking people.
And on top of it, psyche is sitting there.
I told him not to say it.
I told him to not to say it.
I told him to stop saying it.
You don't decide the doctor and he's your mom.
I told him several times not to say that you know, he's like actually said my first name and last name on your panel
And he's your mod and then you get mad at me if somebody said like, you know
Psyche I don't think that you know your nails are dirty. I don't I don't say that to you
If they say you're not taking care of your fucking cat. I don't say that to you
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, you're gonna let that fucking mushroom dickhead fucking sit here and disrespect me and stargazer
No, I I mean I told them to stop several times and then I eventually like you don't tell him to stop you just take him
I did so I okay. Just take it. Okay. I'm on him too. Okay. Okay
He's disgusting
But psyche, you know me well enough. I do not come up
I do not say nothing until I see people being hurt hurt and people are getting hurt hurt over stupid shit
Yeah, and it's got to stop
I want you to come up here and tell me what kind of drugs I do and who are my fuck you said you know
The people I'd buy drugs from go ahead and tell me who they are
But there is nobody that you can name
You fucking idiot. I couldn't buy weed. Oh, you want to know my dispensary?
You want to know where I buy my fucking like alcohol? You fucking asshole. He's a shit.
You know what you think you're allowing psyche is like
discrimination
Disrespect and then you get upset if people disrespect you on my
So it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, so both of us are having like the same issue.
So both of us have the same feeling.
You both already, I don't have like a doctor like fucking J-dog as my mod.
Okay, well, okay.
Read the chat maybe a little bit. Nobody's fucking like though because I have the chat and I've got you guys
Well, can you read like a little bit of the chat? Can you a little bit? Yeah, well, yes
He's a known fucking doctor and you're sitting here and you're like letting you like oh my god
He's like you have any you can you like him to come up, right? You like him to come up right now
Do you want him to come up?
You want a doctor to come up here and tell stargazer that she's the old bitch and I'm a
So I got it. You just asked him to come back up. And so I did not I did not
Are you hallucinating? I did not
Okay, she said the person that was telling the lives could come back up here and tell
He was the one that said that so that was yes, so she didn't say okay
So just just making clear so but I asked you throw me to you right now and you said no
So I won't okay. I'm trying to
I'm trying to be you know, I'm gonna give you a little review about Jay dog. He dogs on
Jamie Rose's sisters. He docks me. He said my fucking last name might he look
How do I ask your father like and Han and marriage if I wanted to and I was like you won't and he's like
So I can't ask mr. Blah blah blah my last name my dad's last name on your panel psyche
He's a fucking known doxter. He doxed on Boston Bridget. He's like a groovy Jimmy Dick writer
And you're gonna fucking sit here and let him sit there and swing his dick back and forth to fucking tell you how horrible of a drunk and
gigantic iron
Did you know he was like, you know, you know, he was uh, he got like uh executed from his x job because he was uh
some kind of a
PO officer that let
and got money and allowed people to get arped.
Did you know that, Saiki?
I don't, I do not know anything about it.
Ask him that, ask him.
Ask him right now.
I bet you he won't deny it.
Free him, yeah, ask him.
He got paid to fuckin' like other people
to get arped in fuckin' prison.
Bita you're gonna sit here and lie on my life. You're gonna lie on that he has I'm a doctor, right? Okay. Yeah, okay. I'm a doctor
You're a hypocrite
Yeah
Can I ask you a question
Did you or did you not have a job where you fucking watch other people getting arped?
working for the government I
Work for the government by the way, okay
Work for the government. No, you're incorrect miss beta
It's not the right time, Casey. It's not the right time.
You are really very interesting.
So you're, like, a provisional officer.
I'm not a probation officer.
I never was a probation officer. I was a corrections officer.
You never ever said that you did that.
You never did.
Corrections officer.
Not a probation officer.
Okay, as a correction officer, did you allow people to get
I never watch anything get down in front of me. Never really never anything happened in front of me. Never
I'm gonna sit there. What's that happen? Yeah, okay, I'm really okay. I just got to go. I look
Yeah, okay, you know, you're like 25 beers in you've been up all night on a live you're red you're raging right now
you'll pass out you'll you'll you won't remember what happened in two three days
and you'll come up and be trying to oh hi psych how's everything going
oh hi and then psych he's just gonna post to be like
like oh like just forget everything happened
veto we don't live on your world bro we don't live like the way you do
and evidently i don't live the way any of you all do
I apologize to you stargazer. I apologize. I apologize. He said it himself either it's true or he lied about it either way
It's very gross behavior
You did it
Cartoon dog time
Time is an alt that's all
But he also lessons and he fucking lit like he hears what you say we all have no time is a bias troll
That's all time is and you're
Well, we're gonna we're gonna get it together for you anybody you believe anybody you believe anything you hear you don't go for facts
You just believe I'm just they just lying to you, right?
But say why you listen to fit stage fit stage
Why is psyche listening to you? Well, listen psyche
And now you're saying why is psyche listening to me?
You're up here trying to dictate to say unmod him right now. Un-do this. Un-do that.
You should be unmodding. You're disgusting.
You're trying to be the person to dictate to psyche.
But he just took out one of my mods and fucking was like, oh, you know what?
I'm gonna say that sherry.
You would never take out any mods.
I'm not even gonna have a J-Doc call me here bitch and like fucking calling a stargazer a fucking bitch.
Call me an asshole.
And hold on fucking dick.
Wait, how much has J-Dog has ever done for you?
Does he have a channel as he donated a lot of money to you?
What does he do except for like,
he literally donates a budget for what he needs as a psyche?
How much should he donate to a psyche?
Way more than you.
Why do you always lark for somebody who's rich but all you do is complain about donations at Psyche Geeks?
Why do you always talk about the money if you're not about the money?
Why are you a fucking doctor and you're a monster?
If I had your money, I would give like you a lot of money, you're trying to kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off, kick him off
I don't understand all the relationships and all the stuff that's happened, and I try to stay out of that kind of stuff, you know, and I don't, it's against the rules, and so, and I was telling him, don't, okay, don't, and I don't know who this person is.
Well, him, like, coming in your panel and saying my last name is and putting, like, my phone number and my back chat.
I'm not, I didn't know that.
You didn't?
I didn't see that.
Keep saying it to you. Okay, so but you said it mean just now so I'm not okay
Do you want to see it? Would you believe me right now if I just show you proof?
Sure
Do you want to see it?
I'm touch if you get to me for any proof. Yes, I'm doxing
It's not it's not allowed on the panel and it's against the rules and it's not it's certainly not for a mod for dogs
Okay, so that's totally okay. I I'm trying to
Thank you. I'm gonna send it to you and I'm gonna give it to you this way
Fuck you and your fucking standards. Don't come on my fucking panel and get upset because somebody says something about you
You're living a fucking doctor and motherfucker call me fucking all kinds of me
And your fucking guest star Gailer. I'm sorry star Gailer. Thank you for like even no, no
Fuck you. Fuck you. All right. Okay. Fuck you
And I would never say that to you. I would never say that to you. I never say it to you. No. Okay. Okay. Well, I guess
Everyone's everyone's gone down off the panel
Well, it's like a guy that's super overwhelmed right now
with everything what it's like a lot it's a lot to
To deal with it. It's like wow. It's all coming at me at once. Okay, so just have a little patience with me if I
I'm a little bit slow with stuff. Okay. I'm trying my best and maybe I'm
Not doing a good job and stuff. I'm trying my best right now here
Yeah, I'm trying my best. Let's see. So people are people are waiting to come on piano. So I will have
Random guy, I mean, I don't you want to contribute and I don't know who this Paul Shepard is but I'll have J-dog in
Hey, thanks for leaving me backstage like for what 15 minutes like I paid for your screen guard for the last
I was kind of I was kind of but I was kind of in the middle of stuff. Okay. It was selfish
It was self
And here's his pulse like anybody know Paul Shepard is get I'm really overwhelmed. I know no
I don't know who Paul Shepard is don't let him up bro. It's a probably a porn dot a porn bomber, bro
Probably a porn bomber
Um, psyche, do you see the hypocrite, the hypocrisy here, man?
You see how she's kind of running you, trying to say, unmod him, do this, do that, do that.
But can you do the same to her?
If you go over to her channel right away, can you go and interrupt her panel and say,
hey, this person said this and this is about me, unmod that person right there and she,
can you do that to her?
Let me just tell you beta is just a user man. Beta is just a user
And I said man, I didn't want no bad no bad blood between like I said
I might not get along with her, but I don't that has nothing to do with your guys's friendship
I want you guys to be friends. I do want you guys to be friends. I do too. I do too. And wow, it's like
Getting over well
And she called me a doctor, but she has black RG the guy who doxxed her and getting the entire live on her and her family
Sending people to her house. She has that guy as her mod
What is she's gonna say that I put that she tried to say I doxxed her name on your panel
When have I ever doxxed anybody on your panel psyche?
Again never
hide, I did not hide anybody or time out anybody, I deleted a few messages, like some messages
last night that I felt were slanderous and so I don't know why this person keeps saying
I did that, okay? I did not, so I need to just correct the record. Let's not slander, okay?
Let's have a conversation. Okay.
Okay. Oh, well, no, I mean, it's a stargazer. Hold on.
I mean, it's like, I...
Hey, both to stargazer, I do apologize to stargazer.
I do apologize for that, Psyche. 100%, man.
Okay. My bad, man. My bad.
I'm mad to admit my fault. It's my bad, Psyche.
I didn't mean to get that on your panel.
I don't know. It's getting so...
I'm very overwhelmed.
I apologize, guys, if I make mistakes,
that I'm trying to do a lot of things, okay?
Okay, so I just want to get things back to the way they were and I got and I don't think let me say
I don't think I don't want to say anything negative about me. Okay, and it's like and I'm sorry like, you know, I
Don't think that she's I don't think that she's these things but I don't think she's about I think that
We're being put against each other and it's like not fair to us and I really like let's I don't know
Maybe I need to wrap it up right now. I'm not much. It's just
Crazy right now. Okay, and I guarantee you this psyche what she's gonna do is probably tell you this
In order for you to be friends with her. She's probably gonna give you an ultimatum. Get rid of J-Dog
Don't ever ever talk to him again. Don't ever allow him on your panel. Don't allow him in your chat
This piece of shit
J-Dog you got a big zit on your nose. What is that?
I don't know, why don't you put it on your camera and let's see what she reflects back there.
Let's see what she reflects back there.
I don't know what she reflects back there.
Well, how come that how come that fucking windows like that? Why didn't you finish your window? Why?
You'd psyched beta read what J dogs said in my fucking
Intention and fucking like I mean I got so much on you J dog in your chat in your chat. You said I was on psyches chat
We're not talking about
There's
Or did you come up to protect your boyfriend J dog is that why you're up here KZ?
Hello
He's not another woman on the fuck
What does he say in my chat?
Oh, J-Dog says all types of awful things about me
Hold on, what?
I see something from my chat, but I don't see your chat video
Okay, your chat, even better, even better for you
J-Dog was up here trying to turn psych against you, that's what he was doing
No, just like he said he's never fucking doxxed me or nothing
Read it
That's a lie
He thought your memory admitted it. He admitted I was there. I heard it
There's two narratives going on yeah, I see it
Give your input random guy you fucking listen
Down your leg you quit trying to sound like you're a tough guy because your voice
You're overcompensating for a small little dick.
It's my voice guy.
Put overcompensating your tiny little dick
and try to sound like a man.
Oh, you got me.
Because this is so fucking...
You have another J-Bog, you fucking creep.
You talk like this, you fucking guy.
So why are you talking like this?
Fuckin' playing around with that.
How am I sound, fuckface?
Really?
There's three speech shots of my chat today and it says
What is that, okay not my name, what is the fucking, what does this say, what does your dog say?
It says, then Bita tries to blame DJ Electra, G-T-F-O-H.
I'm just trying to tell you the mother fucker the dog sir
Yes
Listen to his fucking voice. He's a psychopath, of course
Because no one talks like this
Everyone on numerous occasions that he has software
What the fuck are you doing?
Oh, this slapped the fuck out of you
No, I've seen you in your little cell phone
I guarantee I will, dude. Come on
Cardi, I will, I will for sure, what if you know it?
What? Why are you talking like this?
I've seen you too, you're a fucking, you're both weird, aren't you?
Fuck your mother
Yeah, that's what I do I creep out all the women. It's weird you do why do you do?
Sounds kind of weird to me. Are you an incel there's always so much
Archie or what it's creepy sure if there's anyone on in
I'm sorry
Dude calm down. It's just a stream. It's just a gay guy stream chill
To suck each other off
KZ and go
Oh, so you're the guy who you go to the guy be a little bit more positive. You're very
Send me to the rat. I just came here for music
So guys, why did you send me to the rat? That's what I want to know
You admit it
Random I'm not I'm not go
Why did you send B to the rat? So you're stealing my actual fucking narrative saying that you did it I?
Said that like five minutes ago, and you're still the truth
I need
Why did you send her the rest listen dude reset come back
KZ would you do that you drunk right now?
What's up? What's up? What's up?
No, I posted a short of when I was on piano with him
Yeah, I guess he didn't like it, but I don't see why he wouldn't get him upset
Jada we're talking about you've got paid to dox leader or something like that
Yes, that did
Dox lots of people okay, and he's proud of it. I can just send you clips of him saying so
Yeah, J-Dog, that's like, not, I can't have my mom like say, like, to talk to her, like, and so, you know.
J-Dog has admitted to being obsessed with, uh, Beta for like, six months now.
To the point where it's weird. Kind of like that random guy is obsessed with Paige.
How that's weird, it's really the same thing.
That's not true, Psyche, don't do that.
I got paid, but we're referring to just tell me no, no, no.
I want to see the first thing that looks like that.
Oh, I can't talk with you guys.
Thank you. I can't talk.
Can you can you mute him, bro?
I can't. I can't talk with this guy.
Everybody, everybody, can we talk one at a time?
OK, yeah, we can talk one at a time.
I admit how you've been obsessed with Bita for about three months now.
These you see this guy.
This guy's fucking crazy.
Well, I'm doing so. You're there, Jay Dogg.
I can't talk man when this guy's talking I can't wait to see what lie he musters up, but I'll be quiet
That never happened I would like to see this proof that beta has
It says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it says, it
Well
If you want me to go back and talk about all of the lies J-dog is told over on YouTube
There's a pattern J-dog you're lying
Which one right there
That's a clone account. That's a clone. That's a clone. I don't even write that way psyche. Look at the way look at the way
It's written
This is a long time ago because this is my old logo, so I don't know you're bad for business. That's just
That's a clone account. I don't write that way psyche. I don't write that way
Yeah, that's a clone. I
To see the profile. Yeah, there's a lot of people make clone accounts of me
Okay, so yeah, that's a clone psyche. That's a clone man
Okay, so I mean, yeah, I mean, I guess I get that psyche. I would be the lie. I would be the lie. I
believe beat a hundred percent
100%
You dox beta you dox beta argue. What do you even defend your beat up when you doxed her?
You
Word man, he's saying the P word
Best friends with Tony the conductor
I don't know Tony the conductor, I don't know him, I don't fuck with him, I don't fuck with him, that's what you guys do, you fuck with Tony the conductor, you use that guy to come and fuck with other people, that's exactly what you guys do.
Well, I do know like remember I remember there was a time when like allied master computer was in my chat like in all this
And he was basically there's a spy and you admit it. You're like, oh, well, don't they Tony works for us
And he's he's been sitting in psychies discord probably right now getting information for us like remember that
Yeah
concrete
Way too much going on right now
So it's a cologne account, right?
Okay, that's what he said
I'm gonna I'm gonna actually put out more screenshots of some fucking doc see me
How many cologne accounts are there of you J-Dawg?
You were on my panel and you were backstage and you were in my back chat
You're back chat. Thank you. I don't really know what to do. I'm giving you all the proof
Show proof. Why would you believe J-Dog over a beta that makes no sense?
It's like he's showing his fucking screen like upside down back like uh, it's like rotating backwards
It's you J-Dog. I checked that.
It's a clone account.
It's a clone account, beta clone account.
Alright, you know
I've been really patient and I've been quiet why all of y'all run your trappers
Go ahead man, and likey and beta and the panel I
Won't be back up for two weeks. I will not be called a bitch. I will not be called a cunt
I am. I am. I am. I am. I am.
I cannot do that
Mothers do this to me
Apologize, man, but you know
Because you don't wait in the anticipation lady. I am a woman not a lady and thank you sir
I was being kind
Everybody please
That's the problem psyche. That's what I'm seeing and this is what's hurting me. Okay. I'm I do apologize. Okay
I'm okay
Yes, I take it personally I'm human I have a heart and like some others that do not
Well, I'm sorry KZ called you a cunt. I do apologize for his awful behavior
But you had to repeat it though, didn't you so that you're not
See how you're doing you're playing games and I'm too old and yeah, okay
My 55 year old ass ain't putting up with that. That's the case maybe you need to question what you're doing here if you're that sensitive
If you're that old, yeah, you're that fragile. You that sensitive. Maybe this is not the right surroundings for you
But you do that. Do you do what's best for you? Honest? I wish you well, and I'm sorry KC said that to you
So you can't even keep your trap shut for a second
There you are with what you're trying to fucking say then miss slowpoke
Okay
Let's let's let's let's. Yeah. You know, he's. And I can't. I love you. I love you. And I will talk to you later. Okay. Yeah. I cannot be ran over like this. I won't. Okay. I've made it through hell and come out and I'm not going to be walked on. I understand. I understand. I apologize. And I mean, I'm gonna, I'm gonna wrap up the panel. Okay. I don't really care either for what it's worth.
Okay, and I'm just gonna wrap up the panel and I'll let me just I'll do like a short reading for the
Casey, why are you hurting this lady's feelings? Okay, so every thing you do guys
I'm gonna what is she what did that kind old lady do to you to Casey you awful person?
Okay, so easy don't talk sir. Don't talk that poor lady. What are you doing, sir?
Casey and RG. I'm wrapping up the panel. All right. Have fun. Jay dog. You lose again
Thank you. Thank you. Okay. So, okay. So, okay. Okay. Wow. And I'll just guys
It's just a lot going on. Okay. I maybe I need to talk to some people one-on-one
It's like, you know, it's so hard with panels and trying to run panels with guys
It's not easy and it's like and there's a lot going on in this community
But you know what? I was at this the good pussy show yesterday and I went on panel
I was literally sitting there for 30 minutes and I did not
Say one word. I could not get one word in because everybody there is basically a birdo, right?
I mean birdo was even in the chat, right? It's like they are just they're just yelling at each other
And I could not I was there for 30 minutes to be on the panel. I did not say one thing
Okay, I do want to pull like five cards out of this deck and then I'm gonna
Go off and maybe eat my Starbucks and
Maybe talk to some people one-on-one. I
I do apologize for name-calling. I have rules in the show. It's other shows again. I'm trying to work things out. I
Please just like I know I'm not doing the best job. I'm trying my best. I want to say no, thank you for
People that are kept respectful and kept it cool, you know, I'm
You know, I'm sorry. I'm not doing the right thing and doing something bad. I
Yeah, I honestly have affection for
for you know, pretty much everyone here a lot of people have been here for months and months and well
I'm it's I don't know all the history
Most of you know each other longer than I've known you and stuff. We pull five cards out of this and we just shuffle it
This is a haters expose and we'll see
It relates, you know you can relate to it. I can read those. We'll see what happens. Okay. Let me just pull five cards
Turn down. Okay one
Two
Okay
Okay, four
Okay, so here's the five cards that came up and so hopefully there's a good message for us and
Okay, so here we go guys
Thank you guys for being here, and I'm sorry if I didn't reply to people in the chat too. Just thank you for being here hanging out
Okay
Okay, we have somebody somebody. That's a fake spiritualist. Okay, somebody
Maybe coming in the guise of love and light that is not in love and light. It looks like somebody
Looks like a broker. We know they're looking through the fakes. There's a fake spiritualist. Okay
There is someone is doing black magic
Juju work on you. Okay, so these are not just necessarily, you know
You know
Woo-woo kind of like, you know magic it can be
Projecting evil eye it can be gossip black magic can be considered, you know slander it can be even the
Yeah, you know doxing is a form of black magic and then the juju juju is something to do with
with voodoo and and
Spellwork, okay, but there could be other
Sporces involved there could be some kind of spiritual warfare going on. Okay. What else do we have?
We have trickster spirit. It says set in loss of memory things end up missing. Okay, so maybe there's some trickster spirit involved in here and
very deceptive and
Not what they seem okay. What else do we have?
We have
Your closest friends hold grudges against you, you know, and sometimes our closest friends can't and
You have to look especially, you know
People close to us can hurt us the most too the closest friends hold grudges. Okay, and finally
We have energy vampire
excessively demanding your attention and emotional support and this can also be
Psychic vampires the energy vampire. This is
This is
Someone could coming in basically to soak up
All this you know all this energy, and I know there's a lot of energy going on too
I think there's so much excessive energy that there's there doesn't need to be really any personal vampires and because
There's the energy is everywhere
They're picking up soaking up some of this energy. There's a lot of negative energy
They're probably soaking up too, and that's not good. That's just let's put another five cards
This one says, spying on you is part of their daily routine.
Okay, so we could have people spying and, you know, just trying to gather information, okay?
And this is kind of like the Joker face, but someone is spying on you as part of their daily routine, okay?
Another five, okay. This one says dark entities are using these people to work against you
Okay, like I said about spiritual warfare there could be you know in the Bible it says you know our law our
works are
Our enemy is not a flesh and blood
but of the principalities and the dominions and
these
Higher spirit could be egregors, which are these
Basically a group with the same spear running all the mines. Okay, and so there could be dark entities
involved in some of this, all right
Maybe you know trying to soak up the energy and maybe for reasons. We all know it. This is spiritual warfare
Okay, I'm gonna do a spiritual warfare prayer after this reading, but how many I have three more cards to do
Okay, this will be a 10-card reading. This is Venus retrograde to dealing with insecurities appearing
Appearance body image wordiness relationship sexuality. Okay, and so sometimes these triggering this triggering is part of
Triggering the insecurities and you know
making people think that they're ugly and you know all kinds of negative things
it's the opposite of the beauty and the goodness of Venus okay this one
says they will play a victim once they know they're losing okay and that too
it can be you know sometimes people will to take the heat out of them
Play a victim and especially if they feel they're losing and then okay, and then finally we have causing you to miss out or lose an opportunity
Okay
Okay, so these are the cards that came up today. Can I there's usually some kind of remedy in these?
I'm gonna pull until I get a remedy. We get a remedy, please
Well, this one says causing you to lose your appetite. Okay?
know that these kind of psychic attacks can't have this physical you know
physical manifestations including loss of appetite and you know there can be
weight loss and you know lethargy and sadness I'm gonna pull until I get a
remedy remedy this one says claiming credit over your success okay
Self-explanatory
This one says okay, so here's a finally the remedy this one says
Recharge your energy this distance yourself take a break vacation pamper indulgence do the things that make you happy
Okay, and it's like in it we can get all wrapped up in this drama verse
Which is really besides the panel verse it is a drama verse and maybe it's good to
You know because I know I've thrown myself into this
Right into all this stuff too and sometimes good to take a break because
When all this energy is mixed up there can be a lot of misunderstandings there can be a lot of heightened emotions
What else do we have?
Okay, and okay. We have two more. Okay hating on your spiritual and psychic gifts. Okay, and this one says
possess an amulet and have it blessed with protection.
And so there's maybe the ultimate remedy is possess an amulet,
have it blessed,
and maybe this will give you some protection, okay?
I would say find a symbol or a piece of jewelry
or something to carry and have it blessed,
either you bless it and sage it
and put some frankincense or incense over it, right?
Let this be a symbol that is a shield. Okay, let this and let just imagine that it's protecting you from all this
it's it's it's making you like a
immune and
Basically a coat of armor now. Let me do a spiritual warfare prayer
I'm gonna do a good spiritual warfare prayer, and I know I do know a very good one
I'm gonna read it and then I'm gonna
Take the advice of going to recharging my energy because you know, and I know this is
Draining on everybody, okay
Wow
Guys, you know, it's like we can take a step back
Take a deep breath. Maybe we can look at things in a different way and not react
Definitely me included. Okay, so I'm gonna do a spiritual warfare prayer
And I'm gonna this is a prayer for everybody and this is to protect everybody because I think that everybody here needs
maybe some angelic intervention and
me included and
I think that this will be a good way to wrap up this show,
and so let me read this prayer, okay?
Okay, so here's the prayer, okay?
It says, and okay, so, and I've read this one before,
it is great, and whether you, whatever your religion is,
you know, you can just ignore or adapt it to your own,
but this is maybe a little bit Christian-oriented,
but...
believe that it's a good prayer, okay? So, okay, so it says, let's begin. As God's
official legislator and law enforcement agent, I come in the name of the
resurrected Jesus Christ, who I am and who I serve.
that at the name of Jesus every new shell bow of things in heaven and things on earth and things under the earth and at every
Tongue should confess that Jesus Christ is Lord. I affect and enforce God's original plan and
purposes over and against the plans and purposes of Satan.
I decree and declare that in this battle, no intrinsic, which is internal, or
extrinsic, which is external weapon, be it emotional.
financial, social, physical, psychological, interpersonal, spiritual, or organizational,
formed against me shall prosper. I place upon myself the full armor of light and of the Lord,
the truth to cover my loins.
the breastplate of righteousness to cover my heart and chest cavity, and the gospel of peace to cover my feet in Jesus' name.
Father God, the shield of faith to defensively and offensively cover my body,
the helmet of salvation to cover my head, and the sword of the Spirit, which is the word of God shall cover me.
Finally, the covering of the Lord Jesus Christ and a robe of righteousness is my portion.
In Jesus' name, the glory of God is my reward.
I decree and declare that the weapons of my warfare are not carnal but mighty through God.
I pull down strongholds and cast down vain imaginations and every high thing that lifts itself against the knowledge of Jesus Christ.
My thoughts are now subject to the Lordship of Christ.
I speak that God's anointing destroys every yoke in my life and that my soul,
spirit, and body now function in order according to divine systems of protocol.
I decree and declare that I am healed and spirit-filled, sickness and disease are far
from me.
I establish divine parameters, boundaries, and borders, and legislate and establish the
laws of the Kingdom of Heaven to govern all activities within.
I overrule, disallow, and veto every diabolical sanction, subverting activity, injunction,
directive, mandate, or order that opposes the will of the Lord concerning my life,
my ministry, and my family.
In the name of Jesus, I nullify diabolical decisions and rulings concerning my ministry,
my life, and the lives of my family members, friends, and associates.
Spheres, stratospheres, hemispheres, atmospheres, realms, regions, and domains.
I dispossess master spirits and employ Michael, other archangels, and the angelic hosts to
handle any satanic contentions, disputes, strivings, and resistance concerning this injunction.
I declare successful divine and angelic undertakings undergirding, reinforcements, and assistance.
According to your word in Psalm 103-20, angels now excel in strength to marshland, protect my
personage, property, and possessions. Yehovah, gibore, contend with those who contend with me,
fight with those who fight against me, take hold, shield, and buckler, and stand up for my help.
Draw out also the spear and javelin and close up the way of those who pursue and persecute me.
Clothe yourself in your garments of war.
Muster your devices, gather your weaponry and ammunition from your divine arsenal.
Make bright your arrows, gather your shields, and let vengeance be your ultimate goal as you overthrow the chariots,
horses, and riders. Let terror strike the hearts of my enemies and cause their hearts to fail.
I decree and declare that by you I run through troops and leap over walls.
You are my God, the God who girds me with strength and makes my way perfect.
It is you who makes my feet like hinds feet, giving me stability so that I am able to stand
firmly and progress on the dangerous heights of testing and trouble.
You set me securely upon my high places, you teach my hands to war, and my fingers to fight,
granting me supernatural strength and abilities, so that my arms break a bow of steel.
You are my rock, my shield, and my strong tower. You have equipped me with the shield of your
salvation, and your right hand establishes me as a victor in this battle.
Beat down the enemy give me his neck cause me to pursue and overtake them until they are wounded and consumed
Falling at my feet never to rise again
Establish my name in the heavens. Let them who hear of me submit and obey me
I announce that it is you Jesus who have blessed me. It is you who
Empowers me it is not by my might nor by my power
But by the spirit of the Lord for when the enemy shall come
in like a flood, your spirit lifts up a standard against him. I forbid and disallow further
opposing activities of any satanic personalities with diabolical assignments concerning my life,
ministry, and family, and I wage war with them. I disapprove and prohibit any demonic interception
I resist satanic intentions, intentions, provocations and negotiations concerning my life and my soul
and superimpose prophetic purpose and divine destiny over and against all activities and opposing
forces that are contrary to the will of God in Christ Jesus concerning my life.
I bind satanic harassment and rebuke satanic concentrations.
I bring to a halt and prohibit all satanic surveillance.
I lift false burdens and remove feelings of heaviness, oppression, and depression.
I cast them aside upon the Lord who sustained.
I shall not be moved.
I decree and declare that, by the anointing, all covenants, contracts, chains, fetters,
bondages, proclivities, and captivities that are contrary to, oppose, or hinder the fulfillment
of God's original plan and purpose are broken.
I am liberated from generational, satanic, demonic alliances, allegiances, soul ties,
spirits of inheritance, and curses.
the blood and the spirit. I speak to my DNA and declare that I am free from any and all
influences passed down from one generation to another, biologically, socially, emotionally,
physiologically, psychologically, spiritually.
Or by any other channel unknown to me, but known to God, I resist every spirit that acts
as a gatekeeper or doorkeeper to my soul, and I renounce any further conscious or unconscious
alliance, association, allegiance, or covenant.
I open myself to divine deliverance.
Father, have your way now.
Perfect those things concerning me.
Firewalls, smoke screens, and a bloodline form, hedges of protection around me and hide me from the scourge of the enemy, familiar spirits, and any and all demonic personalities, making it difficult, if not impossible, for them to effectively track or trace me in a realm of spirit.
There shall be no perforations or penetrations to these hedges of protection.
I release my name into the atmosphere and declare that prayer warriors, intercessors,
and prophetic watchmen are picking me up in the realm of the Spirit.
I speak that they will not cease or come down from their watchtowers until their assignments
have been completed.
I decree and declare that they will conduct their intercessory assignments under the direction of the Holy Spirit in Jesus Christ, who is my chief intercessor.
I decree and declare that the Spirit of the Lord is upon me, the Spirit of wisdom, understanding, divine counsel, spiritual, supernatural might, knowledge, and an utmost spirit of Jehovah.
As I advance, I am divinely empowered and increase in skill and understanding.
I obliterate and annihilate satanic impressions, illusions, projections, perceptions, suggestions,
suspicions and deceptions set up as a decoy or an ambush to my soul.
And those assigned to pray with me, for me, on behalf of me, and those who work with me,
are assigned to me and interact with me daily.
I forcefully resist the wiles of the devil and prohibit the hijacking of divine thoughts,
inspiration, revelation, insight, wisdom, knowledge, and understanding emanating from
the throne room I have with me, Father.
Especially those who initiate, stimulate, sustain, and reinforce my kingdom authority in the earth realm and in the heavenlies and who facilitate God's redemptive purpose.
I put to a halt all destructive, disturbing, and destructive measures.
For this reason was the Son of God made manifest that He would destroy the works of the enemy.
I prevail against Satanic inhibitions, prohibitions, and all limitations.
I decree and declare that all invisible and invincible walls are destroyed.
I execute divine judgment against Satanic demonic activities,
and I war in the spirit of Elijah and Yehu.
I disapprove, nullify, dismantle, cancel, and forcefully oppose any satanic operations
maneuvers, manipulation subversions, strategies, tactics, plots, plans, and ploys that are
designed to hinder, prevent, frustrate, foil, deny, or delay God's original plans and purposes
from their quick, swift, and speedy manifestation, particularly in the correct time and season.
I prohibit the alteration and changing of any time or law that is concerning my life,
I move synchronized and syncopated to the choreographic, symphonic, and orchestrative
movements of God. I establish that if laws, statues, codifications, bills, charters, and constitutions
are changed, they are changed in my favor so that I may prosper in the place of my assignment
and the land which I am domiciled. I decree and declare that
My times and seasons are in the hands of the Lord and they shall not be altered or adjusted by anyone or anything.
I function under the anointing of the sons of Issachar, and God gives me the divine ability to accurately discern my times and seasons.
I decree and declare that the eyes of my spirit function with 2020 vision for correct understanding and interpretation of divine movement.
My ears are in tune with the correct frequency of the Spirit, and I have clear transmission.
I decree that this day I operate according to God's divine timetable and calendar.
I decree that God's agenda is my agenda.
I am not my own.
I have been bought with a price.
I therefore submit myself to Him alone.
I declare that, like Jesus, I come in the volume of this book.
It is written of me.
Overthrow the plans of troublemakers, scorners, scoffers, mockers, persecutors, and character assassins,
expose satanic representatives, and grant unto me divine strategies and tactics
to identify, resist, and overcome plots and plans arranged and established for my demise.
Draw out your spear and stop them in their way. Let them be confounded and put to shame. Let them fall by their own counsels
Let them be turned back and brought to confusion. Let them be as chaff driven by the wind
Let the angel of the Lord persecute them. Let their way
be through dark and slippery places with the angel of the Lord pursuing and
afflicting them. Let them be put to shame and dishonor who seek and require my
life. Let them be turned back against doubt if you plan my hurt. Let destruction
come to them suddenly. Let them fall to their own destruction. Let destruction
come upon them unaware. Let them stumble and fall into the very destruction they
have contrived for me. Let them be wounded and destroyed by the very weapons
Let them be caught in the same net that they set for me.
Let them fall into the very pit that they dug for me.
Let them be hung by the very news they constructed for me.
Let them be burned in the very fire they have lit for me.
Let them be consumed by the very beast they have prepared for me.
Strike them down in the very act of their mischief.
Let their mischief be returned to them twofold.
Pluck them out of the dwelling place.
Root them out of the land of the living.
make them like a wheel turning in confusion, make them stubble before the wind, make them
as wood burned by fire, persecute them with your tempest, cause fear and tear to grip their hearts,
let them become founded and troubled forever.
Wow, this is very long and so I'm just gonna go right to the end I decree and declare this prayer and all future prayers take on the
characteristics of divine projectiles in the realm of the spirit and that they hit the bullseye
I decree the laws that govern this prayer and all spiritual warfare strategies and tactics are binding by the word and
Blood and by the spirit I decree that every spirit release from their diabolical assignment now becomes a part of Jesus's footstool
I seal this prayer in Jesus of Nazareth's name. Amen.
Okay guys, thank you for listening to the prayer. I love you guys. Thank you so much for being here.
Let's remember this is the internet. This is
not necessarily as it seems. This is not as serious as it may seem. Let us
I'll be protected, let love fill our hearts, and may everybody be blessed, and thank you
for being here.
Have a wonderful day, and I will see you later.
stands where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom